They came to the altar. They gave me.
The strings already knew the name inside me.
Letanji. Open the mouth.
I was talked to-
With a storm in my chest
A smile like a doorway nose
Long hair on my shoulder
Old thunder and deer
Voice that the world never heard
The mirror held the face
I had carried so long
But somebody greener was humming my song
A parrot cried once
From the dark of the room
locked word and my body came loose one string one spark one emerald breath
beauty step forward awaken my flesh the hail broke open felt her I'm in the shape
of a word thunder under hidden with me I spoke my own name asking which body was
true in the city margin start singing my toenails and no sovereign stands alone
Impossible stands here
My parrot keeps secrets then
Nice bang!
Fractures and still holds
Looking for surviving the
Continuous
What are you doing there, brother?
That wasn't bad with I and X on it
I got no comment, I'll be honest
You did no comment on it? Okay
How are you doing there, brother?
How's everything?
What do you have to speak about today?
What's up?
I have another copy left
Thank you, Benette, thank you so much
So, you're praying, yeah
Hey, FreeSide, how are you?
I like FreeSide, FreeSide can have a mod.
I was looking for that.
I had a modwatched people because I had all these rogue mods
and so I just slowly get in a room game
in your dreams and there will be a mod again.
I was thought his name was FreeSide.
FreeSide?
Yeah.
Okay, so I think I got all the,
well, if you can make sure you get another chance,
even though I'm being sarcastic, I might just do that.
Okay, okay, so.
What's up? How do you think that is? How are you?
Are you doing candle?
Well, I mean it's up to him. I can't force him.
Is he banned? Is he allowed?
He's allowed. He's not banned.
Okay.
I call him John, John, John, John.
So how's you, so Arthur, how's everything going with you?
Are you on camera the other day?
Yeah, let's talk about that, brother.
You know, I just get the fuck out of here.
Nah, I'm just kidding. Come on.
You know, the one-mop thing.
Y'all lane.
Yo, is this a new shirt?
This is like a pajama top.
I've never seen this shirt.
You've never seen this one? Yeah.
It's like a pajama set I had.
I remember pajamas.
I remember shorts.
It looks like...
Have you ever seen Barney?
Barney Frank, the gay politician.
The dinosaur.
Oh, no. I was too old for that shit.
I do know, I know the song.
Do you want to sing a song?
The song is just, look up the suit, it looks just like your shirt.
Do you remember, do you remember his, he had this friend that was at Triceratops?
It was a woman, what was her name, baby?
The yellow one?
Yeah.
Oh, body, oh.
I forgot.
That better name, but he had a friend that was a yellow Triceratops thing.
The kids were like the worst actors I've ever seen on an E.T. show, you know, it's like...
Oh, come on.
Barney.
Oh, anyway.
So, it's a Lingus Pinned.
So, you know I have memberships again.
I'm a re-monetized Arthur in an exciting news.
Oh, shit, nice.
Yeah.
You have to be careful, though, with the A.I., because they strip it away with the A.I. news.
No, no, because I thought that's what it was.
I mean, I thought maybe that's what it was the first time.
And then I had an outside analysis done of the channel and stuff to see what caused it.
And it was because I had too many shorts and so it was duplicating my own content for my lives onto the shorts and so there was too many of them.
And so all I had to do was hide a bunch of them and then I got it back instantly once I was able to apply.
Because I had to wait for my strike to expire.
So it's all good.
full
Good credibility and good a good standing with YouTube. I actually have some really cool
Icons too of some some emojis for the members of stuff. There's trip to simple out here. Yeah, I mean everyone's allowed here as long as they're respectful
I mean, it's like I mean it's like I
I'm banned literally every single person again, and I mean now now if it's saved already been revamped
But let me see if I can put on these icons and see, oh yes, oh and they're locked, I have to draw, okay so this is a different account, I think it's cool to say this name right now, okay.
Yeah, so I'll check right, try to post these icons in the chat, I'm not sure I can do it, okay.
So they're really cool though.
I think Kitten Cakes is a member and a bunch of other people.
I got awarded one of my gift memberships I got on myself.
Kitten Cakes was at Cumsy the other day.
She was, yeah.
She's really nice.
Super nice.
Yeah, we played a really funny Howard Stern appearance
last night.
I think the retard was hilarious.
Speaking into my account.
Let's see, okay.
Jake, do you like the thumbnail I made for today?
Let's see.
You can't see it?
Hold on, oh, what the fuck, I guess.
It's pretty good, huh?
Okay, so here's the emojis, so there's this one.
And there's also like a little member icon,
so these are good, okay, there.
This is what we got so far.
When I get some more members, I can add some more.
So there you go, pretty cool.
Yeah, there you go, I think it is.
Don't they look cool?
They're like really cool.
They're like, you know, really nice little stylized.
and the emojis and then the members see like you know this is a little a little
um he gets the receipts next to his name so that's what the members get bigger
that icon and they just had a high thing that is hey and Preside some
bonnack I'll shout out to my mom's members been free Said is his name dude
he was on the show last night he was really funny actually I just like had
laughs he just laughs I love how people laugh emoji the brown nails okay I'm
gonna do I'm gonna do a broom gig emoji with
His butthole. Yeah, I'm gonna make this, I'm gonna make this one as you upload your Broom Game, take this picture, I know you love this.
Wait, why does Broom Game not like you? You keep sitting on here.
It's Sam and his brother.
Yeah, but like...
like so what they're like they're high-minded they you know they're they're partly
designing each twin it's like I'm really like this the picture of my I have is
like pretty shocking like just because my sister probably doesn't like something
doesn't mean I'm gonna do the same thing as her I mean I made a Kate I made a
Kate puppet look yeah come on let's leave Kate alone she's nice that's nice
it's a nice puppet over a nice puppet
And I made I made a I made an I next one too. I don't know if she likes it or not. I forgot but here
Okay, he says he hates people. I know mom. It's all good. You just hate everybody
Okay, that's I yeah, I get it. Yeah, that's valid. That's valid. I wanted to do a thing that is mucket
I think but I don't know I did I did a ghost muppet too. He's my ghost muppet
Oh, what is this that goes supposedly is no longer gonna come around here. Oh, he's just he's
He's being stupid. He'll be back. Did you say that because I am next for saying that? Well, I talked to INX already and we're fine again
I mean, it's like it's uh, what?
We're fine. That's that's just the coolest one that I make any other ones
And you know, I mean big like this one's a classic one. Are you guys truly good? Yeah
All right, she used to go to panel radio. See and that one's their legs, but I made them up at version of this one, too
Which I like the Muppet version too.
It's really cool.
I don't see it.
I don't know, maybe I lost it.
But yeah, so that's what I've been working on lately.
It's my art.
Yeah, oh yeah, here it is.
This is the Muppet version of it.
See?
I don't know.
I dance, I dance too.
Things change very fast for me.
Literally when she left the Beatles,
because the Sam M, then she called me
and then we had a chat.
All good, I know I was I was there I was right I was there or those war dogs legs
The tape saying my war dog on there. Yeah, it doesn't play a word. I like there's a heat
There you go. Yeah, it's coming up. Yeah, I think
Hello there
Hi classy, how are you?
Hi, so how did you like the appearance?
I think that was pretty good.
How did I like what?
You know, INX on Vitas, I think that was pretty good.
You know, I know you don't care for INX too much, but.
The thing!
She's very transparent, that's all I'm gonna say.
Okay.
How are you doing there, Billy?
Good, man, how are you doing, Arturo?
It's good to see you around, brother.
How'd you get back on Vitas?
Um, she had a poll the people voted and I was honestly surprised that the majority wanted me back
I know I gave a whole speech. I hope you can tune in and listen to it back again
I don't know may I ask you would you have voted a yes or no?
Yeah, I would have voted a yes. I'd like you or whatever you know that you know at one point. It was actually
67 to 43
How's that that's 110 no, or sorry, I'm sorry for my math 37
Okay, that's even better. I was I was honestly surprised. I'm like how I can't believe it
Then she kept blaming me doing all it's just like come on stop enough
Good for you. You didn't have to pay 25 bucks. How did you vote Arthur? Tell me I only voted once dude. Come on
Per count
Come on. Stop. I'm just
See now you're being rude now. Can I be rude to you? I got to give you a jab back
No, because it's my show
I mean, I think I've had better appearances lately. Yeah, I've been able to stay calm. I've been able to be heard even Christine like got like rage quit.
Which is like I didn't try I wasn't that was my goal, and I don't know if that was actually I don't it wasn't strictly because of you though
Yeah, yeah
She's just like you know she raised quit
She's always like trying to get me to quit and stuff like that at this time. She quit without saying but I wasn't even that means there
I was just
You know, like, and then everyone was like,
in Kate's show, they were saying,
oh, Saki's so dumb, like, he was doing this stupid,
like, sweepy imitation that he got from Arthur.
Like, it's not even funny when Arthur does it.
And then he calls good times and he thinks it's funny
because good times is falling for it,
and he talks to him sexually for an hour.
That was funny.
That's one of the best-
Who was there?
That's one of the best good time show there ever was.
I mean, it's like-
What?
what when I was sweeping for an hour on the phone wasn't that funny come on let's not
good times it's one of the best moments of the show I mean it's like you know
this show is horrible I mean it's uh just sit here and talk about you know water
you're not stupid you're just like you're out of here joe shipply
wait who would have ever thought psyche can do a man's voice
I can't. I have a deep voice actually. I do have it. You know, sometimes it goes a little high.
You're not bad at impressions. I mean, some of them are pretty good.
This is a brand-new Q-space whenever I go live. Oh shit, no.
Hold on. How about my impression about Christine?
Okay.
The thing that is, what do you want?
that's pretty good too I think ours is better it's we be better than mine too
but the thing is it's like I forgot about sweetie hold on hold on come on hey
psyche hi hey thing a good afternoon guys if you would have done that voice
Um, I just wanted to say that I will be taking a break from you. Oh my god
My voice was like a little scratchy cuz I like I've been yelling
Okay
You know sweepies
He's our senior on beat us, you know, and yeah, I mean it's a guy. He's uh, he sees her on beat as I'm sure he was always a fetus
He was there today when I turned on on beat us. Yeah, good time to sitting up there, you know, and it was like, oh my gosh
You're glowing your aura
Okay, well, I know well, maybe he's better with that alcohol. He was on beat us today. Yeah, I saw him on beat us
He's over a piece
And then uh, oh, yeah, so I got Dolly Parton. So you know, so Dolly Parton this brings up to to mind
Have you heard of Dolly the sheep? Um, yeah
Who's the other one that just died someone else just died?
Well, Tim, which is name. That's it. That's it. Tim Curry. Tim Curry. Tim Curry died. Oh, yeah. Yeah
Same age as Dolly. Oh my god. I know that he's that old. I mean, it's like he's using a lot
He was he played it right? Yeah. Yeah. Oh my god
And that is going to be haunting dreams and stuff.
He was a great character.
Well, I mean, I liked him.
Yeah, he was cool.
Do you ever dolly the sheep, though?
OK, you ever heard of a game?
There's a game called Gabriel Knight.
I don't know if you've ever heard of that.
Have you ever heard of that game?
It's called Gabriel Knight.
There's several, it's from Sierra.
I played all these Sierra games in the 90s.
I remember the Sierra games.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
King's Quest, Lugers of Larry, Space Quest,
and a bunch of other games.
Yeah, I forgot where I was going with that, but yeah
Wasn't it easier to shoot Larry a Sierra game? Yeah, it is. Yeah, it is. I played all of them
When I was little I played them and it was like wow, they were like so explicit and I remember. Yeah
I remember it was it was
Stimulation for a bit. Have you heard of that Arthur? Well, these leaves is it Larry? No
It's like in the 90s, they had these like, you know, there was hardly any computer games
There was like one company that was making these really amazing ones and
These two layers about this guy. He's an apolly. Yes, sir. These are suit. He's always
Please quest. Oh, yeah, I've played the police quest games, too
Yeah, and he like he's always trying to get laid and he goes and like it's all
All these bizarre women and stuff like that. They're all trying to get laid and he never quite gets laid, you know
but I'll stop it beats beats stop stop it trip
You guys were going
You guys were going good. I didn't need to jump on I was doing stuff anyway
I'm talking to Tripp and not in chat. Okay. I'm sorry
Yeah, so I'm trying to... Oh, Phantasmagoria, I played the Phantasmagoria to Roberta Williams, yeah.
And there's also a game called Laura Boe, that's really good. They put just a couple of those.
But I pretty much played almost all the Sierra games.
They would come out and like, they put all the games that came out, like five or six of them and one package, you know, but some of them were like, you know, really...
There was one company that would make like the war games where you would go on like...
bombing runs or, you know, those term, you know, perfect wargames.
Yeah, like, uh, something of civil, class of civilizations or something like that.
No, no, no, no, not quite like that. There was civilizations there, but.
Okay. Yeah, I mean, it's like, I mean, I got, I had a computer when I was, I think, let me see,
I think I was like 14 or 13 or 14 when I got my computer.
and uh me too yeah even younger there's never the same you know whenever the
Atari whenever the Atari 400 came out that's when I got my first home
computer this is raining cue when I'm ever go live this is his face oh shit
keep thinking I'm gonna put it up on the screen but I don't know I have someone
Okay, never mind, and that's hardly a home computer, but whatever I had I remember I had a 486
Oh, okay, and in school. We used to have computer day. I think like every Friday 486. Oh my god, aren't you fancy?
There are two started with the 286 is you start with the 286
Well, I was my first one was a 46 by 1993 or 1994 it didn't have I mean it had a I don't think it had a modem
I think that was my second computer
How do I finally like the little modem you want to the bowls and boards and I remember on GA well you remember acoustic couplers
Accused acoustic acoustic couplers. It was a device and you would put your phone on it and that that was the modem
That's how it would communicate with with sounds you could hear
Yeah, I mean it's like I I don't think I ever did it like that, but yeah, that was something
Yeah, I mean, I mean, that technology is coming very far.
Remember when they say, the thing that is, when you're a kid that used to just put like two cans connected with the string and that was your cold, your cold with the phone?
I don't know if I ever did that. I guess at some point I must have.
I don't know if that worked. That doesn't work too well. I mean.
No.
Yeah, you have to start.
If the wire is really, really, really tight, you might get some vibration like passing some really, really deep.
Deep frequencies, but yeah, you're not going to get full speech
Yeah, well
Do you like to stir radio shack? I remember that. Yeah, I didn't mind it
I don't have any more of them. They don't have them anymore not up here. No
Why you still haven't done there, um, I guess I haven't seen one for quite a while
But I mean I haven't been to a mall or anything for quite a while. So
I don't remember when they used to sell the radio shock computers to the PCs. Well, yeah, I mean, it's like and
You know those were good. I mean
Radio shock was great. You could go in and you can buy like what they got all the parts. Yeah
They had all the little parts for everything everything
If you were an electronics nerd that was the place, but I wasn't an electronics nerd you aren't no
Do you ever wear thick black glasses?
Thick glasses, no.
But I do.
I need to wear glasses to drive.
I don't really need to, but I have to,
because of my license.
So yeah, I guess I need to.
I could see you being like an evil scientist in a movie.
You said the professor from William's Island
is kind of like that.
I don't know about evil.
Maybe risque.
You're wrong with that guy.
I don't know about evil, but maybe pushing the boundaries.
No, I wouldn't have the attention of wanting to destroy humanity or anything like that, but I would just be pushing the boundaries like oh
What if I did this what if this happened?
What would you do if you so if you could if you had a power becoming invisible?
What would you do first would you go to the women's locker room? I don't know. I'm not 14 right? I mean
Well, that'd be a couple of course I'd spend a couple minutes in there, but it wouldn't be my hangout. Oh, where'd you go?
I don't know
But even the physics of that is
Makes it questionable. I mean if I'm invisible that means light passes right through my retinas
So I wouldn't see anything right now now. We're getting very meta into like the superpower kind of thing
I mean it's like right, but it's okay. It's okay. You know, I've been like a fly. It's kind of like I have to like jump
Yeah, I've had those, you know fantastic thoughts when I was younger too
If I were you, you'd pretend you're a wizard?
No.
You're like a coven of witches, you never imagined that.
Could you imagine if you lived for like, you know, thousands of years?
Huh?
Like, after a couple thousand years, wouldn't you just be a fucking miserable, depressed
person?
Like you've seen everything you've seen like the worst of humanity
You've seen everything. I mean you would just be miserable. So what does that picture?
What about it?
Well, why we're wearing a wizard robe is trying to our wishes
Yeah, I don't think I need to point out how real this photo is
You see Bita, it was Bita right there.
Yeah, well, come on, let's.
Because you used that picture of her where she's like,
but Kate looks so different.
Like, Kate doesn't look like that one on the left.
That's like a, that's like a.
Let's, let's not talk about Bita.
Come on.
No, Arthur's, Arthur's a little white guy.
Let's just be a little simpy again.
You're a little simpy, Arthur.
You're feeling a little simpy today.
I'm just.
Trying to do good
I found out that she's one of the higher ups, so who's one of the higher ups she is
That's you
Me look cute Nancy. That's what I still look cute. Where the fuck are you?
What's that mean?
Well, I mean, you're like, oh, she's the higher up like she's my boss. Yeah, I found out she's one of the higher ups like
Wait, whatever says is law in the community. No, I
Never voted for her. I mean exactly. That's not what you wanted the dictatorship. Yeah, she's Iranian
I'm not ruled by Iran. What are you?
What kind of American are you?
Well, you know, you got the theory you Arthur's are you saying you've got the theory like you're on
Anything that psyche says I do not agree with noran. She doesn't as if she were to she follow the wrong
Leadership, yeah, I have to do the disclaimer now to Arthur. I told you that's right thing. That is we have to do that
Yeah, higher-ups only apply to Sam and because he's a retard. Yeah
Higher up she was a Sam and Sam and I'd be a clips. Yeah
Baked lips by the way
I think it's a I think it's a big lips
like big lips. Yeah, you know, it's like if I was to kiss
Arthur for like 20 minutes. It would be what?
Hold on hold. Whoa
What I'll say that. I mean we all have our fantasies
What the fuck I'm good you're here. I can't decide cuddling with Arthur in a uniform
costume. Just a lion. You're a clown, man. Hey, who's talking? Listen, Linda. Listen,
Linda. Yeah, I don't know. I'm gonna tell you there isn't so much trouble. Okay, let
Yeah, what is that my face? I thought you were a black port Puerto Rican woman. Oh, yeah, that's right
Yeah, I'm turning into a Puerto Rican woman, Arthur. Do you know about that?
Those are the worst
See okay here here's this is a picture of me as a Puerto Rican woman. Oh
Do you think?
isn't that the widest Puerto Rican woman you've ever seen Arthur? I haven't seen her, that is the widest Puerto Rican woman you've ever seen Arthur, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her, I haven't seen her,
Yeah, the thing that isn't funny, but it's been the cracking jokes
Do that one already did that
So now we're we're pen pals. I know it's me, but it looks slightly different. It's like something's changed in my face there
Well, yeah, you just got but but sex
What?
Very satisfied
Little bit comfortable. It's a dirty cell. Yeah, clean it up
little cake
I'm just kidding, I'm just kidding.
Okay, I'm just kidding.
It's a dirty cell.
And then I have, oh, here's Brandon Key when he,
whenever I go live, this is his face.
Someone needs to make a gulp on me for beat his nose.
Kingston Pan, yeah, sure.
Someone should do it.
I should know.
Let me see what else do I have.
You're seeing, let me see.
Or this is what Alice McQueen looks like.
Every picture of Alex like every AI thing. He's always looking mad
Yeah, he's a one eyebrow. He's a one angry eyebrow. Oh
Oh our door
Arturo, okay. What else do I have? I have um, I have pictures of golden girls like that one. I just about you don't like that
They look nice
Sam and looks great
Okay
You have
Sure, same man going to the freak off. It's kind of like it looks like Barry white
I keep saying that he just looks like a white Barry white
You know from there. Yeah, or Latino Barry white eyes are too straight. Yeah
See, I don't like to hate me like she makes me like bald like like and like tries to say I'm like Syrax is like
I'm worse than Syrax or but I mean please. Oh, here's it. Here's them. This is Amanda Squarepants. You know Amanda Squarepants
Oh my god
And then I have safe huffed marshmallow Amanda somewhere in here. Here. She is. I can't oh here. She is
Have you talked to ghost since last night?
Hmm, I don't know. He might have called me last night. I don't know. We have no no, okay two nights ago
He calls me. Hey, hi. Oh, I'm sorry. I don't call much. Oh, I know how are you doing?
I'm just worried about you Bobo and and he's like then he was like I was like
Well, what do you want and that cuz he always had like I'll turn your motorbeats. Well
Oh, no, he's a great sort of panel, and I was like,
okay, well, I was like, do you want me to sort of panel?
I said, I will, but, you know, I'm not an ornibay.
I was like, but, you know, maybe throw a super chat
or something like that.
And he's like, oh, I'm gonna get the name anyway.
So I started the panel, and he didn't come.
I waited for like two hours, and he didn't come.
Yeah, phrasing.
Maybe he didn't show up.
Okay.
Show up all over my face
I was like, who's the predator, a chemical, chemical cuddle that sounds like a South American
God?
Who's the predator?
Are you?
Okay.
So he didn't show up.
He was wasting my time and it's not the first time he's done it.
He does it all the time.
He'll go, oh, come to this panel and I'll be alone there with all these chuches.
I have no idea who they are.
And they're all like, oh, you're like the guy that goes and I'm like, oh my gosh, it's
not a friendly place.
And he just leaves me there.
And he does the same thing to INX too.
Okay, and then he showed up last night
Right. He didn't show up last night. He didn't. Or yeah, he did. Yes. He did last night. He did. He did? Okay
Yeah, I was on panel with them for a brief period
I fell asleep last night, and then I know later you did. Yeah, then my whole episode got
Because you were playing that fucking Alexander club remember I was up here, and then you started playing and I'm like, oh my god
I can't do this. I can't listen to it
Well, and I fell asleep and then you kicked me and I left I didn't come back
I checked back in later and there was some movie or something playing in the background
Is that what it was I think so I got cuz I got like oh shut up Daniel
This is this is oh, we have we're brandy Q. I know the alts now. So sick. So anyways, so ghost came by and there were some
Words not directly. It's like he was talking in chat or something. Yeah, he's a little bitch
So you haven't talked to him since last night
No, and he's always complaining. Oh
He's I mean it's like
The thing is it's like yes, I have like said
What's up with the donations because he keeps asking me for favors and stuff
But he doesn't like like okay. Well if he was like donating himself. Yeah, I wouldn't mind like, you know
Pavilion these favors, but I've still been fulfilling them
You know, and he's not a penny. I mean, it's like maybe he feels his past donations carry forward. They don't I mean
You gotta let him know that that was over a year ago. I mean really make them understand almost goes to over again
I mean, it's like we're I mean, it's like 10 months
Then I mean, and then he's like, oh, I can't do it because you don't super chat. Well, they're back. What's his excuse now?
I mean, seriously
ridiculous hey guys don't remember actually um you become an
initiate so I guess Arthur's not coming back oh well that's
just that well I came up here specifically to talk to him you
didn't yeah well you can't you can't talk to me what's wrong with me
I'm not saying I can't talk to you I'm just saying I you don't want to that's
one way to put it no I mean I'm just me that I came up
To talk to him specifically. That's all
He was gonna glaze IA next you heard that and then she she went off on him
She preempted his glaze and so he was like fuck you then that was funny. Yeah, I
Wanted to glaze IA next again dominant
Why you always get so sexual? Oh, you're you know, I think about doughnuts. Why'd you bring it to sex?
Don't know what you meant. We know exactly what you meant by that
What a glazed donut wait, it was a glazed donut like disgusting because it's like no, I like glazed donuts
As long as it's not too much glazing. It's not because then it's just like it's like diabetes inducing
What was under disgusting
Can't hear you never mind never mind, okay
So how how's the wife?
She's an ex. Oh, you're I know you're you're divorced. Oh my gosh. I'm so sorry
It's alright
Do you still talk to her? No, it's been years
It's gay marriage legal in Canada. Is it legal or illegal legal? Yes, it is legal
Okay, we marry me. No
Please see what I said, please it. No
It's legal. It doesn't mean I have to be gay married
It's not mandatory
Yes, it is. No, it's not
What happened with Arthur? I don't know
Arthur's just a bitch
Oh, oh, oh, Sarky, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Well, he's a fine woman on her period. It was a tampon string hanging out. Shut up. What the hell man?
I said a thread not a string
Same thing. No
No, I found a picture of um
This is like this is that guy Rocky Dennis and who he goes on the vias. You seen this guy? Yeah. Yeah
Jesus
That's nasty
Rocky doesn't look like that
That's the real Rocky Dennis. That's how Rocky not our Rocky. Why would he take that name?
Well, because people told him that he was looking like that, but that's just that's being I mean that's excessive
He doesn't look like that. I know but he obviously
Things that he he didn't do anything to me. He didn't how do you know bake lips?
We've been there the entire our entire relationship. You've watched every interaction. I've had with him
So you can you can say that definitively or you just talking at your ass
Dumbass who's that Arthur? No, I'm big clips. No, but talking about who Arthur no about that other person. I'm rocky Dennis
Okay
Yeah, okay, I don't think
He calls me animal abuser and so I mean I can't stand these people that just call me like these things that they don't know me
They don't even watch me and then they like just listen to like some dumb ass like every
lying about me
So so that's it. I mean, it's like, I mean, I mean, it's like, you remember that F-A-G-G-O-T
Kazoom, you know that guy Kazoom? Yeah, I know him. So Kazoom goes on beat us and they're all saying
Oh, we think psyche's on meth or whatever and then I come on and everything and then I like, you know
Kind of had my like, you know, like little spurge appearance, whatever and he's like, oh my god. Oh
He just freaked out. He must have been having a meth psychosis, and did you see the sores on his face?
He has meth sores or AIDS sores or something.
Yeah, I remember that. I do remember that.
I mean, what did I ever do to that?
F-A-G-G, I mean, what, what, what, like, G, he's like, oh, and he's, and he's gay, he's
supposed to be, like, on my team or whatever, but it's like, oh, it's about loyalty from
gay people.
I mean, G.
What?
I mean, most of these gay people are just like these, like, big clips, there's, there's
go where the, where the wind takes them, you know, just because, like, I mean, does
that mean that heterosexuals all back each other too, just because they all have the
same sexuality?
Yeah, they're all sitting with each other.
Stop it.
Well, yeah, I think yeah straight people and yeah, they put themselves in a group
Team straight
Yeah, but they don't just
Like have each other's back just because they're straight
Well, they're against a big
Person should have another gay person's back just because they're gay and I think that's gay
That's ridiculous
Well way to go around
Well, I want to show you something that is absolutely shocking not gore is it no are you ready?
Okay, Arthur come back fuck sakes. I'm jumping soon. Okay here watch this
This is for this is for a big close. Is this like a long video right now? No showing me a picture
I just don't find that funny at all. I don't know. I don't know what the humor is in it.
I didn't laugh. I was getting around. And I'm someone that sees the humor in everything
and I just don't see it there. Maybe you just don't have a good sense of humor. Maybe I'm
No, I have a very good sense of humor. Like I said, I can see the humor in just about anything
But that to me was just it was uncomfortable
The woman was laughing hysterically because it was a nervous reaction because she had no other fucking thing
That she could do at that moment. She was probably
She was embarrassed as fuck
Have you had sex with a dolphin?
It's even like you're just gonna test it
or traumatize or something.
I mean, it's supposed to be fun for all people to watch.
And you're usually seeing that
like the sour puss look on your face.
Okay, whatever, like, you know,
like you said, I wind all the time.
So I'm just, whatever, dad, whatever.
You're talking like, I'm just being you, I'm just winding.
Yeah.
Oh, I mean, that's your default state.
I mean, it's like, I have to teach you
to put a little bit of, like, oomph in your voice.
You're mad.
That's right.
So I'm just being me. Is that better? No
Maybe someone else, please
I'm just gonna be someone else's how you just said maybe the thing that that could have been
Was that the thing that could have been what about it?
Can you change your name to that? No
What do you mean that could have been is it too long? I'm just thinking in variations or the thing that may be someday
No, man. I already am I already is
I already is but your bakelips has your name the thing that was I like that too
Yeah, that's bakelips though. As long as you know that or as long as you know, it's not me
I don't it doesn't matter who it is
So what else I guess Arthur's not coming back
Good
I'm just kidding. I like I like I like Arthur. Oh, there's something there's a thing that could be I think that could be
So there already is one thing that is you can't be that name
What if you married the thing they could be then then would their name change the thing that is or would you change your name to the
Yeah, at that point that would be is yeah, they would be is
Thing that is thing that is that's what it would be and I come to the wedding
Well, there won't be one
What if I said if if we were to marry and I'm telling you well we won't you said it
You said gay marriages leave on Canada and big clips. So again, it's not mandatory doesn't mean I have it ready to go
He already has his name
perfect so there's no there won't be a wedding oh sorry won't be saved well
have a you know my parents didn't have a wedding they went to like some kind of
like you know legal office or something like that it's still a wedding I mean
it's just not a ceremony they don't have the ceremony or traditional wedding
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
fuck man he's got like kids all over the place he's oh my god he's fucked yeah he's messed himself up
well yeah see look at i don't have a i don't have a wife nor nor kids and look and i'm still poor
i mean imagine if i had a wife a kid a wife a kid i'd be homeless
Um, so, I don't know, so, fourth or fifth, well, yeah, I mean, it's like, you know,
we're going to do the Elizabeth Taylor numbers here, you know, it's like, I think that's
what he's going for.
I think he's battling Elizabeth for the title.
Really?
Well, okay, so Dolly Parton died, so I have a short presentation about Dolly Parton.
Um, she was actually a, um, a clone, did you know that?
Oh, stop it.
I don't want to watch.
Okay, I'm going to jump.
Okay, bye.
Okay, see ya.
Oh, I'm going to jump.
Good.
Make it from a high place.
I'm just kidding.
That was the other term.
Okay.
It's a bungee cord.
You know, like Christine says,
professional bridge jumping in Canada.
Okay, so here's the video.
Let's watch together.
Hello?
Extendo.
Oh, darkness, my old friend.
Hello, Extendo, my old friend.
How are you doing? I'm great. Look at me
He's great crossing his legs
Uncross those legs
That's how we sit dude, that's how we say we said what our legs spread farther you got to spread your legs farther
Like that, yeah. That's how men sit.
It's actually like a preprosate exam or a gynecological exam.
Joker's not in rehab. Joker wasn't in rehab?
No, I wasn't in rehab, dude. I'm not in rehab.
I don't enjoy ball crushing, no. I don't like crushing my balls.
I got this vape in the mail. It's one of those that you got. It has two of the flavors.
Yours has three. Mine only has two. I got this one from California. Yep. Joker is ignoring
Joker's a straight guy dayclips and it's like he doesn't like to be sexualized by a big fat gay slob a
ball stretcher
Only I only if you don't have you you do it to me. We'll be by my balls stretcher
So one of my chambers already gone see
Bonter one chamber. Yeah
Damien says you're bi yes, we know you're but we know what you know is bi
big lips
No, I might be a little metrosexual, but I don't think I'm bi sexual
Well, you metrosexual is like right on the cuffs, but you finish you finished with the transgender
Okay
Maybe I am
As of lately I really like women
Maybe was just a phase. I believe that you I believe that you will eventually, you know be with a woman
and
We I'm not sure if you'll ever like, you know
Call for a diamond to have some drinks with you guys or whatever. Oh, no, you wouldn't do that
Never never never
Who is that ball guy that was on here a second ago? Oh, that's a mr. Clean, you know the from the cleaning products
Yeah, I was having a product endorsement. That's the thing that is you don't know the thing that is
No, I have think I've seen him before. He's a legend. He won't even beat his life
he I think he's in love with beta and
And he always like oh be da oh, and then she's like
I have a clip about her bitching at him on Sam and Sam in there. Let me see. It's on Sam and in front of the
I got so high yesterday so I got passed out you did I wish I was
There with you. Okay, so okay here it is this channel. Let's see
This is called Sam and her friends.
This is Bita, I guess, who's on the channel.
Well, yeah, this says,
Bita's kiddies put her life in danger with a stranger.
Here we go.
Let's see if that does it work with Bita.
The end of Bita.
That's just a call I mean, you know, but.
Well, I mean, you know, we were concerned, you know.
What are you worried about?
It's worried about your safety, okay?
Well, my safety is a lot worse on the internet people in real life are fucking cool as fuck
That's what I mean, I was concerned for your safety
I cooked three eggs or for
His dog and his dog was the sweetest German Shepherd in the world
I didn't even need to cook that but he liked it and he ate all of that
Fine. That's good.
So, I mean, what the fuck are you worried about?
Or are you worried when people were sending comments to me?
No.
Yes.
Like, how can you?
No, you weren't.
At least a stranger told me, I explained to him, I was like, this, this happens to me and he was just like, these people are saying this and this and that. And I was like, yeah, this is what happens to me. And he's like, I'm right around the corner. You ever need help. I'm here.
eat up but we we don't okay i didn't know that and you're alone with a stranger okay
that's why i do everything on panel everything just fucking gravy fantastic even down to the dog
look at look at my cut look at my cut there's cabin tearing you're like what is going on they
Fine, it only takes a moment for something. Okay, so yeah, there's cavaturing
Listen, if you don't want anyone to give a shit about your safety, just say it
I don't want you to give a shit about my safety
Don't give a fuck go get the guy go get the guy again. Just go grab some guys
Why don't you go get uh, why don't you go ask uh j-dog and psyche it's a stuff that fucking doxing
Why would you stop saying you love Kate and I like Kate?
I never said I love Kate.
You think I'm worried about Orange County people that do deliveries for me?
Why are you giving me such a terrible experience?
They're literally like dumbfounded about what I have to deal with.
I can't believe this, I can't shit, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can't believe this, I can
I don't have no issues with you. I don't like argument.
No, no, no, no, you do know.
That's the thing, like, I don't know if you get this or not.
When I'm on my zone, I don't want to have any discussion.
I don't. I don't know what you're talking about.
She's in her zone. She's in her beta zone.
I disagree. I think you do have some kind of issue with me.
I don't know exactly what it is.
I think the thing that is, is, I think he is in love with me.
Yeah, I've said several times I love you like I care about you. I want you to be
I don't have a romantic interest in you, but I do
It's so fucking stupid because I only know you for
Yes, this is the dark web you're as for it. You're as join the panel you're as
The thing that is dude the thing that is I think he's a simp. Yeah, even if it's in a platonic way
He was simping so hard for beta and beta literally denied all of his sympathy
Yeah.
He was like, Vita, are you OK?
You're all alone.
Vita, Vita.
She's like, I don't want you.
I don't like you.
It's great to watch.
I know.
I mean, it's classic.
Room game is no difference.
I know.
You know, Sam-Man has a brother named Broom Game.
They're like obsessed with, like, clumsy and, like, you know,
sex with brooms and...
Yeah, so when clumsy was in prison
He was there is a man that had a broomstick and he was a part of a rival tank
And the rival gang member wanted to stick a broom up clumsy's butt to prove to everyone that clumsy wasn't about shit
So they held clumsy down ten of them held clumsy down and they stuck a broomstick up his butt. Yeah
prison prison war
Christian gang war I know I mean if they did that to me that'd be like a fantasy for me
I'd be like I think it would probably hurt. I think they made it where his butt was like
His boasty was not tight anymore where every time he fart it just sounded like nothing. Oh
We have a guess someone's tough in French over one second. Are they here to confront me? Yeah. Oh, it's Chris gay Chris gay
How are you doing? Are you okay Chris gay?
Chris K. I mean, it's why I'm in a wheelchair now, man. Hey. Hey, can you say, hey, no, don't burn my banking this time
On the last I of course. I want to eat
I saw me Chris K. Row with my energy
I'm not in a wheelchair, bro. I'm even to stand up
Can you turn around? I want to see your back. I just got I just got paralyzed last night, man
Yeah, you're getting another fight with a dwarf.
I'm sorry.
Hey, gay clan.
We're a gay clan.
When I started gay gang, it's just for LGBT people, I guess.
You guys missed it.
My homie, my homie Q, was just over here, but he had to go like, yeah.
The black guy?
Yeah, he'd go back to his pad to make sure his girl was all good and shit.
He's like, he said he'd come back.
We'll see.
Yeah.
Hey.
I got it.
Got Starlink coming in the mail bro Starlink. What are you gonna do with that?
By a spy on people what is that for why am I touching my ball? Oh my god, you can see me
Well, because
He was touching his balls
I don't want to get into details, but like my connection is going through my wireless
uh, dad on my cell phone through a tether dude, so, you know what, hey, did you guys
see my god damn kick stream last night?
Oh, do we see it?
No, I missed it.
Oh my gosh.
I can't believe I missed it.
So what happened on it?
It was a while.
Yeah.
No, I ran in the fucking yo-yo.
Yo-yo-yo with this?
You mentioned this person named Yo-yo.
I'm not sure he's a guy or a girl guy.
Hello?
Yeah, I randomly ran into him.
He was doing the gas station.
Like, I guess they puked him and his friend
puked in front of it.
And like fucking they came out and said you know fuck you or like clean it up or whatever
He likes he like disrespected the gas station guy or whatever in fucking so like uh
I literally that's literally when I pulled up on him a shit like uh
No, I like that's but I came up on him. It's weird. It's weird because I was uh, you came on him
No, like my idea listen Joker my idea is like this live stream and go around and you know some random people be like
Hey, man, have you seen like an orange cat around here or whatever?
Like I just lost my cat my girl, you know, and fucking uh, they're like, you know
Oh, what's his name or whatever it like have him start calling Mike, you know Albert?
Yeah, I mean he I just see them right here
Like have these people like that my cats not lost but like have them
I started looking for my cat and he was like I got a picture like pulled my wallet out
you know show him a picture.
I mean it sounds the premise sounds kind of funny but at the same time you're probably
It would be funny, but it does lose the orange cat and the alber, I mean it's like the cat
passed away and it's kind of sad to be telling you.
Well I'm bringing his legacy to you, but I did it.
Maybe if you did it like different accents, like you're from different countries.
Do a walkie-round like that, go.
How do you do that walk?
Well, that's that's why I didn't want to bring my selfie stick to do IRL because I wanted that because I listen
I was I was literally like, yeah, I was like, yeah
Yeah, I'm looking for the cat, you know, like I'm talking to my girlfriend
So it doesn't look like I'm live streaming like what I'm more right there
I'm like, yeah, what do you want me to do like the fucking I'm like looking I'm asking people, you know
And they think I'm talking to my girl like on FaceTime or whatever, but I'm actually live streaming, you know what I mean?
So they think I'm actually looking for my cat, you know what I mean?
What did they figure this out? And they see you're just like, you know, fucking with them and there's no cats.
I mean, half the people I did it to is like, man, you're cat fucking, you know, there's a lot of straight cats around here.
He's probably not getting laid or some shit. That's what they say.
I'm like, man, I got to find it.
My girl's tripping out.
I'm like, yeah.
So that's what you did on your show last night?
So you went around asking people to look for your cat?
Yeah, and then that's when I came across Yo-Yo,
and then the whole shit switched.
So what happened with Yo-Yo?
Tell me that story.
I had the gas station because I guess that, you know,
because the vibe that he had me on, the vibe that he don't
on it, because he was streaming also,
the vibe that he deleted.
I wanted to see like his perspective like fucking if you go look at my bro. He's like like yo yo bro like fucking listen
I've got I've got way more pull on this shit than you homie
Chris K is a moron. Yes Chris K is more
Why are you big clips once and saying that I'm ignoring them big clips?
I'm only responding whenever there is airtime to respond first K has been babbling for a minute. Yeah
I mean, what do you think about is the idea for the show? I mean, I I don't know if I would I
Don't think it's a good idea
Actually, I suddenly called yo yo, but there he is. Oh my god. Look at this guy. This guy's hot. I love this guy
I actually called yo yo Oreo. So now like we really just chatter column Oreo. So that's a new meme
Can you ask your friend to come flex for me real quick? I want to see your yeah, tell me take your shirt off
You're on a gay show and you can you please um Bobby's cute. Yeah, he is
Yeah, baby, let's do a line
Hey sexy, hey listen, this is my buddy the right joker. It's sexy, but this guy right here. Hey Papa. Hey Papa
He's got that he's got the fucking iphone 17 pro bro like why would he want to listen to you guys Bobby?
Bobby sexy Bobby
Super I'm extra gay. I'm so gay that I fucking like I have two rainbow flags
That's okay, but it's okay every experiment with a guy
Okay. He's under straight guys. He wants your boasty. Yeah, I'm under straight guys. Do you want to do a threesome with Chris K?
Myself? I can make it happen.
Threesome with him? Yeah. I love you. I love you. You look dark chocolate.
Bye.
Boys
Hey, you know if I wasn't from Jamaica why else would I wear this hat? Hey, well, you're making me crazy. Yeah, so Bobby
You're making them horny. Yeah, you're making me horny Bobby
Bobby you're Jamaican because you're Jamaican me horny
Well, let me finish what I say, bro
Yeah, like yo, yo fucking uh, I was you know go go on like play the ball play the ball just skip through it real quick
Oh, your kickbot, it'll get to link me to it.
I mean, I say, hey.
It's like, I'm gonna go make a sandwich.
Okay, dude.
I'll see you in a bit.
I mean, I'm gonna.
He's a joker, the whole beat.
You should make a sandwich.
You three make a sandwich together.
Yeah, I would be in the middle of Bobby and Chris K.
See, I gotta get Kisha.
Hey, Kisha, hey.
Kisha, where's Kisha?
Is Bobby like Puerto Rican women?
Because I'm going to turn into a Puerto Rican woman.
I always say, like, you know, Keisha, hey, man.
Hey, Keisha, bring him to my fucking party.
You know what I mean, puppy?
I thought you brought Keisha over here, you know what I mean?
Damn, cutie!
Oh, you all right?
I'm sorry, Bobby.
You're a team, and Rod just got pissed off.
What happened?
Nothing.
They were, hey.
I was just kidding, Bobby.
No, it's something else.
OK.
No, I say that's nothing to do with that stream, bro, that's nothing to do with that shit.
That would be a good thing, my personal shit.
First of all, I'm sorry, Bog.
Yeah.
So, Chris, what did you guys end up to?
Oh, it's streaming.
Where's that girl?
Go to my kick and replay my stream real quick.
Did they find that woman's body yet?
What woman?
That woman, that witch that was in your house the past few days.
Oh, uh, Bree?
Yeah, Bree.
I don't know, man.
I hope she's all right.
Well, all I want to do is help her bro. Fuck you. She'd like fucking
Did she steal your wallet? No
She stole from you
She stole
She stole my fucking S9 that had S9 and it had a buster fucking fuck
It's old but it had hella pictures dude that fucking
I didn't have it saved her will ever you know and fucking when she should miss you after she stole it
She came back and I thought my darling. I was like, you know, not not every deal that what she came back
I was like, hey, where's my fucking phone? You stole my shit, bitch. She's like, oh, I still have it
I was like, yeah, well go get it. You know, I mean, yeah, I was like fucking go get it. Yeah
Well, maybe she just didn't have service
No, I just use the Wi-Fi
No, I mean she fucking took it to the one of those goddamn automated things and sold that shit
He said she gave back to you. Oh, dude. I'm still waiting. She's fucking she took me. She took off
Yeah, but you know, but I know people that know her type shit, bro
I'll miss you. She's good. I'll see you know listen if she ever wants to come back in here
She better be stuck on my dick like I'm on the way in
Does she have cheese?
I mean, of course.
Yeah, exactly.
Right?
Yeah, you're just gonna fucking be like, it's okay because of head?
No, you're right, you're right.
I mean, I'm actually like, little part of my-
There's more principles about this shit.
Fuck head.
In the little part of my brain, it's like fucking, you know,
I hope she actually still has it, but I know it's-
Bro, you know, when's your birthday?
I'll buy your fucking pussy for me.
Coochie's really stressing you out like that.
He has a pocket pussy. He has one. He showed it to it pretty.
See that's crazy. He's still stressing over Coochie like that.
I've never even used one.
Yeah!
What's up?
Yo, where's the thing that is?
He's in the shop.
We're here with Bobby and Chris K.
Are these guys here? Like, are they on panel?
Or are you just watching a stream?
Yeah, dark channel. Yes.
Like they're on full screen this is the first time
This guy's YouTube channel. Okay. Hey, psych when you get banned on YouTube, bro
You're welcome to come to kick or rumble, you know, I've been I've gone past it like it's five times
I've been banned five times back every single time. So I'm gonna monetize that too
Let's make some money off this shit. I'm making money now
YouTubers do like they upload videos. So you're not making money. Sure. Yeah, I am off the stream
Yeah
Well, I mean of course not bring in big big big. What's up? What are you getting like $5 checks or what?
$10 no, I was getting well
I got demonetized a few months ago, so I just got remodeled but before that I was getting like over a hundred dollars a month
You know hundred a thousand oh
$100 bro, I make that in fucking two hours
a real job. I was making 500 a month on Rubble. That's not enough, bro. I get to waste my time
streaming with this shit. Yeah, Bobby can make some money by modeling. He's so good looking.
Has he ever done any new modeling? Come on. He's super good, bro. I know it's cool, bro. Damn it.
Yeah, Bobby makes 500, Bobby you can make $500 a month at least on chatterbait.
Chill, say chill dude.
That's just a loan you have to do when we're working.
Hey, if I get on chatterbait I need $5,000 a month.
Okay, well we'll do it.
We have 500, that's payable.
You have to get one of these things you put in your butt and then people can, you know,
make it vibrate.
I need some butter in my mouth.
What the fuck?
Ready to do this?
You know what I mean?
Let's all do it.
Yeah, yeah.
You can stick a gun in me as well.
You don't want somebody with a book like me to ask?
Just because I psyched what it is.
Bobby, you guys are going to come move in with me for a while.
No, please don't let his gayness get confused with me.
No, it won't confuse you, but there's no clothes allowed in my apartment.
It's an old new apartment.
Like, he wants me to like...
What's the other guy, bro?
Talk to me, my guy.
Arthur, are you to be there too?
Who's good, my nigga?
What's up, buddy?
How you doing, family?
What's good, my nigga?
How you doing, man?
Yo, I heard you were locked up for a minute.
Yeah, it's all good, though.
We out and about, living a life we free,
living an American dream, smoking tree, drinking beer,
that's what's up, that's what's up.
With my fucking white supremacists.
Yeah, well he is racist
He's racist, but he'll do gang stuff and he has a black best friend
I'm not fucking that guy, I'm a pussy, that's what I'm talking about.
What is this?
Frankie, you told Chris K what this guy's fucking.
You told Chris K's friend what Chris K told you about moving in and everything?
Yeah, Chris K once he said, he said, my friend Bobby and I will move in.
We'll do chatterbait with you.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm just playing as them you said and he said he looked at any Bobby said he'll
submit that with me Chris. No it's good to think about with a jail like we
locked up fucking right now it's like fucking this is this is like I have
beers. Oh I got beer. Wait slow down. But you're selling can make you an Oreo cake
and I'm fucking like it reminds you of how the hell shit he was so you don't
want to go back. That reminds me.
Just talking about just talking about I never said no, you really wanted me about I loved it
I love jail. I love jail. The showers are great. The guys were hot. I want to get drunk
I can't get drunk until I want to get pruno. You just make it in the toilet. You just put a bunch of fruit in the toilet
You know who Samann is
Yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
I have a sexy picture of Bita, hold on a second.
Yeah, can you show us?
No, I don't get it on my own.
Let me do that.
Here you go.
Come on, Buster.
Jesus, she looks like that one American when we
debuff her with the bandana.
We are pretty much an American play with the woman,
but she's like, I see.
You know what that is the most famous like American woman like the rivet
rivet girl whatever she's like hey hey say seriously he probably does have a
he has a what
You got you probably have a natural fit. Can you can you speak off? Oh, yeah, I mean weird. Please don't show nobody
It's not in this fight. I'll be strange. No, I'm not sure. I mean, I have
Okay, here's well hers here's her gotta get her fucking her her her like come on her
What is it? Yeah, I have lower faces covered here
I agree with you say like look she's not here to fit herself.
Yeah, you know what I'm saying, we're just showing off and shit.
I think it's a good picture.
I wonder where it is.
Hey, I don't doubt it's none of them, but like.
Here, here, her face is covered in this one.
Yeah, this is perfect.
Oh shit, is that Clombs?
Who's Clombs is here?
He's in chat, yeah.
Clombs.
Clombsie!
That's my brother.
Clombs.
Do you like juggalos?
She has her juggalo makeup on.
Yo, twin!
Yo, hold on. Can clumsy join? That's my twin.
She down there look like 60.
Yo, twin!
Twin!
I still can't keep up.
You're fucking 48, 49.
I'm 40. Come on, bust one.
How old are you, Bobby, in your 20s or 30s?
Yo, twin!
What do you think? How old are you?
Bobby, do you like a massage?
Hey, what's this guy a hopper or whatever fucking you and you and psych like you guys want to make a bet. What's the bet as long as long as it's not gay. What's up like his age like you guys got you know what's his age like fucking whoever gets closest like fucking you know.
I see. I see. I see. I see. I
see. I see. I see. I see. I see.
I see. I see. I see. I see.
I need to close my door, this guy's a fucking weed whacker outside.
Hey, you hurry up, bro.
Hold on, how come?
How come Clumsy couldn't give me a shout out?
Damn.
Look at this motherfucker.
He running a panel over here?
What, dude?
What is Clums, bro?
I gotta be showing my dick right now and getting bad on YouTube.
No, like, he walked away from his, you know, shit.
Like, there's people backstage at Waha.
Oh, they can't hop in because he's on them?
Yeah, he walked away.
Oh, there's a limit on this one?
I didn't do it, bro.
We just had seven people in a party, bro.
Listen, when I do my panels and shit,
like, I stay here and I make sure that it run it right.
Like, you go downstairs?
What do you go downstairs to?
Yeah, that's right, bro.
You even walked off the camera several times, bro.
I'm not going to sit here and lie on my knees.
Well, no, this is, if he's running it,
I have nothing to do with this.
Oh, he's the host, and he's running it?
Yeah.
No blame.
You never know.
to try to say what's up and you're like downstairs or whatever you know. Come on man. Yeah.
The guy's like, okay, I feel like three seconds. Oh, one, two, oh, he didn't like it, you know,
he didn't bring me on. Okay, I have some pictures I can show you guys. I'll show you some pictures
of a eclipse. So he's a photographer for the community. So he has some pictures you put up.
So, here's Bayclips' page.
Okay, here I come.
And these are some pictures of people in the community.
I think Mr. Xlendo's on there.
Here, I'll just see everybody.
What is it?
Mr. Xlendo, that's a crazy name.
I have no intention.
That's why I had the camera, or the camera.
Hey, check it out, guys.
Let me just, let me see, let me see what's happening.
Okay, here we go.
Sharing.
That's what I was looking for.
Okay, so here we go.
So there's Sam, man.
Jesus.
I was gonna say, man, there's clumsy right there.
Oh my God.
Yeah, he drinks lean.
That's not cool.
I don't know what a clumsy line.
That's clumsy stuff.
I don't know who that is right now.
That's Patrice.
Beatrice, whatever it is.
Yeah, that's Bita.
That's Bita.
OK.
That actually goes to Mr. Extender.
That's OG Mike, or is that Troy?
Mr. Extendo's expecting
Shout out to clumsy for not giving me a shout out
Let's be troll I think
There's me. Oh, put the 13 all
up. Oh, man, that kind of do
look like you. There's the
LV. The LV. I'm not sure. I
think that's LV. Is that real
for you? I'll give him my three
inch anything. There's me again.
I'll edit it for you. There's
Bita. That's beautiful. So,
yeah, there's Sam and his
brother, Broome gang. Just
Bita again.
That's Peter when it's over with.
Peter's done.
Oh, it just gets worse and worse.
Oh, that's when she was before she got bad.
LV is Peter again.
There's, oh, there's black guy again.
Oh, shit.
That's Clums.
If Clums was gay?
Yeah.
Fuck.
That's me.
Oh, shit, Shaggy.
There's a broom gang.
There's Q45.
There's me again.
That's you.
Well, it just gets worse and worse.
Yeah.
There's me.
Bobby's like, you know what I mean?
What's that?
Old Hobbit?
No, no.
My thing.
Yeah.
There's SIG.
SIG.
Big Trollah.
There's Joe Shipley.
That's Big Mike.
Actually, that's a good Mike.
Oh, there's SIG that is.
There's me again. Oh my god. Oh, there's a beat right there. Oh, that's a nice
It's that way go back go back go back. Is that actually me that's actually me
Oh wait go back up
Tommy James, you like it?
Oh, that's fake, I've only seen the titties in the movie.
OK.
No, her tits are that big.
Her tits are really big.
Oh, there's me.
I'm real surprised there.
I like that picture.
I'm shocked.
Good times.
Just shipply.
Why are they all looking strange?
There's Broom Gang.
Well, here's the answer.
All the black people look crazy.
Here's the thing, like, no offense, psych,
but this guy's actually had a folder of these pictures
He actually has like a folder of I have I have two folders
I have one of all the streamers and I have one of just naked pictures of Bobby that I brought on the black market
Well, thank you. Can you show him an actual photo controller? I think she's pretty hot. I'm not gonna lie. Yeah
Wait, what happened?
They're talking about a trolley. We're talking about this other female controller. Oh, she's pretty bad. I'm gonna lie
She's pretty bad. That's a fake-ass name
You troll it. Yeah, there you go. Oh
This told me her name is controller
Yeah.
Can you wait for me to control shit, bitch?
I'm going to play you like a video game controller stick.
Ooh, that sounds fun.
I'm going, what button you on?
You want to be right at all?
Left at all?
Just push them all at once.
Ooh, ooh, I got a T-co.
I don't know.
Her name is Big Troll.
That's all I know about her.
This is how I drake.
Controller, controller.
Controller.
I like that.
Controller, controller.
That could have been fucking some lyrics right there, what you just said.
It's real, it's a real asshole.
That was, that was like fucking...
That's a real asshole, man.
I will, I will get sued.
Bobby, are you a rapper?
Ooh, what are you smoking on?
I'm not a rapper.
You think you can rap?
Fuck no, buddy.
I'm a normal, I'm a normal civilian.
You are?
Are you in the military?
Well, I wanted to.
I never made it.
The Burger King wants to know, has Chris tried to kiss you yet, Bobby?
Bro stop that case shit brother. No, I say you being gay shit. It's cool problem. Okay, egg in it egg in it
Egg in it. It's like holy shit, bro. I really just want to take a shower with
I won't touch your phone
I'll have a normal conversation. What is your gay ass like you? No, what do I like?
I like I like streaming I like I like actually be be be be real bro be real
What do I like I like I like doing the streaming thing and having fun and like you know
Partying and smoking money. How old are you brother? You have no what he's gay. I'm 45
Yeah, but Chris is 40, not that much longer than Chris.
Well, if it makes you sound and feel any better, he's fucking 40 and gay too, though.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
We still like him, and we were very gay friendly.
Exactly.
You know the thing about him?
He doesn't pressure.
He's like, take a shot.
That's not gay.
I'm not gay.
I know, I know.
I love pussy, bro.
I don't know.
You eat crackhead coochies.
I love Pussy. Yeah, Crackhead, Pucci, Pussy, whatever you want to call it, he, uh...
I know, you're right, your ass is open, man.
I did.
Can you stick it in? Do you feel anything?
Hold on, can you show me who the controller is? Please?
Yeah, I'm gonna show a control picture.
I'm looking for it.
Of course it's weird, you ain't feeling shit.
You just boom, boom, boom, nothing.
And then you did it wrong, you still didn't feel nothing.
Hey, you know it's bad when you fuck with your mom and you still can't get enough, you still don't feel like me.
Okay, okay.
Keep looking for her, I'll be right back.
Okay.
Oh, we have a guest coming, we have a guest coming out.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Why are you telling bad?
You feel bad for yourself?
Because she's all fitted out.
What's cracking?
What's good, Bobby?
Hey!
What do y'all do, man?
It's hot in a bitch out here, bro. It's hot in a bitch
Now I'm in New Mexico be dark
Yeah, yeah, it's about a hundred degrees over here right now, but I'm almost done you won't do it
I just want to jump on today. I'm up with us. What's up, man? What's up, Chris?
Man, I'm just getting some shit right now, man. That's it. Spinning some shit right now
Yeah
Hey
What's up Mikey?
Later on or something man, y'all say bless man
I think I might, let me see if I have the ability to code.
Let's see, he's seen us on Sykes stream and so you know.
Oh yeah, he's seen us.
So he just wanted to say what's up.
Who's all the big students?
I guess you're the big students.
See, we have 56 people in the chat
that are looking at you guys right now.
And so he's looking at us?
Yeah, he flexed for the camera like this.
He just flexed one time.
Should I flex one more time?
Please.
I'm not even bluffing.
It's okay.
There we go.
You got a little bumpy, you look out of there though.
Wow.
Arm wrestle.
Arm wrestle for me.
What the fuck was that?
It was cute.
Can you wrestle in boxers?
In your boxer shorts?
I've been wrestling.
Fucking, let's say I'm weird at that.
What the hell?
You hit my shoulder?
Yeah.
You hit my shoulder.
Here, put your hand.
Go ahead.
Oh.
Yes.
Oh, well now your wrist was like crack crack crack. I was like, I wrote this whole room. Oh shit. All right
That's why I'm not a football player anymore
What'd you do? I got fucked up
There's an error nigga
You're playing football you fucking fellow. He's tapping me in the air, bro. Flip man. Were you see with it? Yeah
I was a receiver
Let me bro
He ate
So shake one shake shake one Berkeley. I can't I'm not sick one. I can't jump over me
But that was a long time ago
But I see you put it put put do that put that when you're risked by this
I know you got to show the two. Yeah feel the shoulder Chris. Oh
Don't do I gotta bring it back. Yeah
Hold on, hold on.
I was there, I could crack your back.
I just put this shit out of place,
I gotta put it back, hold on, bro.
All right, bro.
Dude, you just, you hurt him.
Hold on, hold on, yeah.
Broke, he broke his arm.
Oh, man, I heard that dog, wild.
What?
Kidding cakes, what's up, bro?
Wow, guys, we're in a wild morning.
Oh!
Oh, I just did it.
Here, you wanna fill it up?
No, no, no.
I don't got too many of these.
Let's do the wrist right here
so they can probably hear it.
The mic's right here.
Okay, that means.
Let's do the wrist.
What?
Okay, the wrist.
Let's take out my whole shirt.
Listen.
Oh my God, Eric clicking.
You can't hear that.
Yeah.
Eric clicking.
Oh, yeah.
That's grinding bones, bro.
Hey, fuck you.
That's the poorest thing.
Did you see the shit?
I'm just saying.
You see these knuckles?
Yeah, you're getting into fights.
Are you like a fighter?
Yeah, I used to buy that.
Wait, how many people still watch it? This is crazy.
There's 63 now. 63.
Damn, we didn't move! Up in the world!
Give me to 100 piece!
We're bringing it. We're bringing it.
At 100, will you take off your shirt?
100 piece!
How do I get to take off your shirt at 100?
Deal.
So yeah, this is so much fun. Like what else you guys been up to you guys going out to like the bars the whorehouses are just
Now we're about to use the fucking lines of coke right now. Are you doing coke? Wow
Oh
Shout out to Chris K. Chris K. You finally introduce us to your boyfriend. Shout out to Chris K. and his boyfriend. Go Phillies.
Is that Sosa? Is that Sosa?
That's uh, isn't that Salad?
That's Elda.
Shout out to you and your boyfriend, man. Congratulations, man.
He's cute, Chris. He's really cute. I'm really good at good things.
He might take it from you. He might take it from you. Be careful, man.
It's my time.
Wait, I'm the other guy, so I'm the other guy, bro.
No, I like you, you're very flexed for me, El, though.
I mean, it's like, it's like, it's been dream come true.
This is the show I've always wanted.
What up, kid and cake?
So, what, uh, Psyche, what happened to you, and um?
And Karen y'all not cool no more are you gonna refund her tokens when she uh, when she
Left me this show today. She called me and we were actually double-dive on and so
She you know she she wants to like kind of a more step away from like the drama communities and stuff
And it's like I don't know I'll support her in that
Yeah, she's kind of like just kind of her words just wrapping up around here. So, you know, okay
Okay, because she says she asked you back for a refund. Is it non refundable to tokens or what's going on with that tokens?
I mean, it's like I'll refund I'll refund them and clap tokens. You know, it's like it's like Disneyland money
It's like once you trade it for Disney money, that's
She can't get it right. It's all over the money gone, right?
Listen, listen
Donations, but it was also like it is certain services
So I think that it's like, you know the laptop bonus
Okay, how many she got left maybe she can transfer them over to me. You know what I mean, okay?
Yeah, yeah, or I'll ask her I'll ask her for you don't worry about it
Okay, what happened with you what happened with you and Christine you did her voice and she started crying on her
She got a little little emotional
Well, she was up there to probably like, you know, call me a scumbag and they'll tell me I mean, she's always, she always shuts me off panels and it's like, I'm interested. I think she can try to get some people to be like, probably be so sad and stuff.
I don't know.
Yo, can y'all mute yourselves, nigga? Damn, we hear y'all in the background, y'all not even talking.
Man, he's just talking to me.
Hold on, Cudi, I can talk all day, bro.
Chill out.
Y'all was having a conversation.
Listen, listen.
It's important conversations that I knew nothing about.
You got a seven-link parlay, bro.
Oh, listen.
I'm in Philly too, cus.
What's up?
You got a problem or something?
Chris K, your girlfriend got a problem.
What's up?
I'm just saying, bro.
You got a seven-link parlay, bro.
You lose it because the goddamn crick are looking at you.
Exactly.
Ah
You sit on the goddamn bitch all season you have to like make a field go from like 40 yards and oh
I missed it like listen if you miss that shit for the win bro like I'm gonna fuck you up in the locker room
You like you fucking lost the game for us, bro like that yummy. Oh, yeah
Yeah, if you fuck if you miss the goddamn field go like in my parlay cuz you didn't make a goddamn feel like
You know, I keep the football do the fucking shit dude like are you see you know me?
I know. You guys play football out on the outside.
Like fucking get off the NFL dude. Like you know what I mean? Like fucking you have you
kick the football through the fucking. No many fucking parlays I lost because
these retards that are kickers can't fucking make you dude. I actually looked them up bro.
And I had my friends fucking find out where they live. Everything. I'm like fucking you're done.
Chris, Chris, Chris, you ain't gonna do nothing, Chris, you ain't gonna do nothing, man.
Well, I found out, like, you know, like, their whole, like, their whole shit, but yeah.
It's annoying, bro, like, when, you know, like, oh, man, you know, and their team members,
like, fucking, you know, oh, well, good, you know, good try.
Like, are you serious?
Like, that's all you have to do, dude.
That's all you have to do.
Hello?
Kick the fucking shit.
Hi, Arthur.
Yo site, did you see a controller?
Do you have a picture of controller Eldo it's a picture controller they can share
She goes she goes like you she goes like you don't listen to hard
Why you got why you got I'm trying to show my non dog. It's a lot good
Oh my god, is that Christine with no with no wrinkles? Come on. So do better, man.
Is that Jadis or is Christine Jadis, Alex Mays, and Sam Mays?
No, no, it's chocolate looking all right. Oh my god, come on, man. Come on, man.
Yeah, it's cute. Okay, hold on. Alex, is that Alex in my ear, right?
Okay, yeah
I have I have um
Yeah, here's a
beautiful
Like NFL fucking kickers like you have to make that row like this
I mean
I don't care about the wind or nothing, bro like you give me like you have one like we sit out there. No doxing. No doxing
No, especially when you lose a fucking seven leg brand when they fucking drop a football
It's just like you get paid to yo
Yo, Chris, I'll put on your neo-nazias outfit your friend seen it. Can you show them?
You know got that yeah, yeah, yeah, that's what I'm saying. He's seen it before you've seen you know, you talk about specs and all that
Okay, he know you racist. Okay, as long as you know you racist. All right
Show the table top again Chris they say you had a line of coke ready man
You know, you know, Chris, Chris, what happened, Chris, what happened with all that?
You don't like specs, man.
You got to speak right beside you, Chris.
What is the white?
What is the Chicano right here?
I do get Mexican a lot.
I understand.
Okay, okay, okay.
Oh, okay.
So you cool with with Chris K saying the hardy are and sit on pan on all that.
I got respect I got fucking respect bro like that. Oh, he does it he calls me that you know
And I'm the same skin tone as you so you I mean, but that's
Same here
You and me got the same fucking hair yeah, yeah, I'm Puerto Rico. Yeah, I'm Puerto Rico
I'm Puerto Rico, but I got the same skin complexion
Bobby and I got the same type of hair and this nigga be calling me Mexican just saying
I don't think it got caring.
But when this shit wet, it'd be like.
I was surprised for you.
What you got?
All right.
That's what's up, Si.
You know, that's what's up.
Come on.
Si, when the AI pops off, Si, you're
probably going to be one of the first ones.
Because yeah, yeah, you know, you use that shit heavy, you know?
Thank you.
Yeah.
We're just busting Chris's balls.
Chris, do you have big balls, Chris?
I'm wondering.
What?
What do you say?
Does he have big balls look like that psych? Yeah
California, okay, okay, cool. That's gay Staten Island
Staten Island brother
He's in New York boy. He's the he's downtown
Down brother Stanton's down brother. We're our own entities
We're our own entity brother. Fuck New York. Fuck New Jersey. We wrap in Staten Island all the way. You heard
Hey, that's that's all you brought in try to do New York accent. We're repping the fucking islanders over here. Yeah, I heard
Well, no, I got it listen
I gotta get a hold of my cousin Bobby downtown and get some fucking cuz he wants
Chris K. What's up? This is Carl. What's up? What's up, Chris?
Wait, wait, wait, Carl, Carl, Carl, I got a question for you, Carl.
Please, please, Carl, dude, we need Mimi to tell everyone what NorCal did to her, dude.
Um, well, all right, um...
The thing is that I don't think she's going to like come on board and see there are my so you've been lying then
All right, my I was not lying. The thing is that she's not a coming in. She's not part of this community
She's not gonna come in but behind the scenes
So how many people watching all right all right
Arthur you know you understand. She's not she's from a different community
They don't do that kind of shit out there. So for her coming in this shit right here, right?
Right, and she knows about this community and she's not gonna come in like get her fucking side of the story
She told me this I her side of the story. Okay, and that's good enough
She doesn't have to get this anyone else. You understand me
All right. Well, my apologies to North Cal
I can't believe I actually believe this guy.
I don't care if you believe me or not.
I don't care if you believe her or not.
I don't care, Arthur.
I'm not here for your validation, homeboy, OK?
Tell him, tell him, homeboy, tell him, tell him.
I'm so, so, so, hey, so, hey, Chris K, what's up, bro?
Hey, homeboy.
Carl, Carl, I got something to tell you.
We're gonna bet remember that bet Chris K remember that bet we made remember that bet
No, but I said Chris K. He's with you. He's fucking faggot you're on the same screen
Yo Carl Carl is the engagement over Carl this elbow big elbow, man
Know what's up?
Everybody clip that shit everything's cool with her and me, okay behind the scenes
Okay, that's all you need to fucking know
Arthur chill out
Chill out chill out chill out. Don't tell me to chill out homeboy
So so so she activated her YouTube though Carl
Let me let me let me let me speak on that she actually did that last month this wasn't recent she did that last
How a trip
That little chip fucker, you know, and then the ones like oh, she reactivated. She unhid her channel by the way now
She's coming back. She's single. No, my poker. You're also subscribed to her. You wouldn't notice it last month
Get the fuck out of here tripping
$20 regular please
Just a subscription list, you know
She did wasn't all of a sudden that we broke up. She's going to go live again. No
And I listen I don't control Mimi. I control myself though. I control myself. I don't control
She's my lady. I'm her man, but I don't control her. I'm not like that. I control myself though. I tell you that
So anyway, so Chris K and Bobby and me and clumsy bet right remember Chris K
That's the fuck the students I'm the Rams fan you fucking tweaker
Hey, no
Clubs, I'm
Carl and I'm a rant and you fucking tweaker listen
You were at the 49ers. Fuck the 49ers.
You're in my division. I remember you.
You said Stithers though. Get it straight home, boy.
No, I said Clumsy's World Team, like that, bro.
No, no, no. Clumsy's with the beers. Yeah.
So you're with the Wyners, AKA 49ers.
Chris K is with the Eagles. I'm with the Rams and so we're gonna bet 20 bucks
He's gonna have the best record so someone's gonna win 60 bucks
Somebody at the end of the season is gonna win 60 bucks. That's what I'm saying
I'm gonna win because the Rams are going to bro
This guy's tweaking his fuck dude
Oh see there you go see the hell no oh shit. He's fucking tweaking. It's fucking tweaker. Listen. I don't care
Boy, you're gonna pay that you're gonna pimp at the end of the season. Let's go
Yeah, yeah
Okay, yeah, Chris. Hey, don't ignore him Chris. Okay, don't know
Back in the days back in 2021, right? So that's when that was a Joss Smith era, right?
so we're all betting right and
on the Super Bowl and looking up Super Bowl and
John Smith owe me a hundred bucks them motherfucker never paid up dude. Fuck
He had the broken, right?
He had the broken?
Well, shortly after that, yeah, he did.
Yeah, he did.
And he was on my stream.
That's when the detective reached out to me.
I had to give him the access to my stream.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I didn't want that shit to go down on my stream,
but it happened twice, two times, two times.
Yeah.
Because I always, always back then,
Aldo, when you're a streamer, you always hide.
or privatize your students, that's just how it was.
Okay, gotcha, gotcha.
Back then, there was no handles.
You can't look people up like that.
So if they look at Retard Ricky,
that's the only impact then, then nothing will come up.
There was no handles.
I
Know it's crazy how to detect this found you though. Did you call it in or sir or they just found you
Actually, I reached out to the deputy of Wisconsin. I reached out to her. Oh, okay
Cuz she was looking for me. So I reached out to her
How the YouTube work I had to give her time Sam's you know when when John Smith was fighting with a she
Holy shit.
She didn't know how it worked.
So she goes, how is juice to work?
I'm gonna send you the link.
I'm gonna send you the timestamps.
You can, I said, what's done is done,
but use it for your investigation whenever,
to close up the case whenever.
Again.
And then I give her a week and after that bro, I close up shot man. I do leave my channel
I mean it's a it's a it's an ox and moron, right? I retorted. I was gonna delete my channel
I was ready going to fucking delete my channel, right? And after that, so after that, I said this is done
I'm done and I asked her some personal questions. What happened with the murders and stuff behind the scenes
I'm not gonna tell you right now
but anyways, after that, he was done, I killed, I zapped, I zapped my channel, I'm done dude.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, it's retired Ricky.
Thank you. Retire rookie, everybody. Thanks, Carl.
No one will shut the fuck up, Saquina is talking to you.
Okay, I'm sorry.
Okay, yeah.
Okay, so Chris, Chris.
Oh, shit.
Yeah, I'm sorry.
We won, we won.
Sorry.
We played, we won.
I was listening to Bobby.
I don't want to hear Carl drone on and on about his full shot.
Bobby, what are you going to ask?
No, we got to make one more bet.
Carl left.
Okay.
Of course, bro.
Carl is getting disrespected, bro.
Yeah.
He's being what you think he is.
I don't know what you mean.
Listen.
There's always a first game of the season.
Right.
That could be the Rams and 49ers in Australia.
Let's fucking bet right now.
I can look it up.
Yo, Kate and Kate, joint panel, I got enough of a Carl for this one.
So that could be the actual first game of the season.
I can look it up.
It could be the Rams versus the 49ers or Winers in Australia.
First game in a season's Patriots and Seahawks.
Who's first?
You said you'd be heading videos?
What is that?
No, I didn't.
Shut the fuck up, you faggot.
I think it's time to get rid of it.
You're not wrong, but you're like two hours late, brother.
If I did, if I did, psyche, how come she never provided those links or those photos?
You dumb fuck.
Hey, attention.
I haven't hit her on Instagram.
I'll ask her.
Wrong.
Right, right.
She has you blocked, you asshole.
She has you blocked.
Yeah, she does.
Right, right, right.
She's watching you, asshole.
It's time to get rid of him.
Let's get rid of him.
There we go.
Go up.
Carl, you've been clapped.
We're right here.
Oh, no.
Precision.
We're still here.
Boom.
I'm sorry.
Hey, I'll make sports best with you.
Oh, no.
But by when I get to kiss Bobby?
What?
Yeah.
We're right here.
What about El though?
This is tomorrow?
I don't want to kiss El though.
I want to kiss Bobby.
Damn.
Oh, man.
We're Carl Bo.
Carl left.
He got clapped.
We can start from September.
Scroll down.
Yeah, I annex I annex
We're parents you're not here how she clapped them. No come on
Why are you lying brah shut the fuck up
This is my panel
Imagine telling the birthday boy to shut the fuck up
Yeah, bring it back for a couple of minutes. I got you bring it back
That who left it all flashed you yeah, then he leaves like
That's a good start, that's it. I think and if I should start doing that roll number one, you don't disrespect psyche on his panel
I think the wait, who's uh, where's the bears playing listen to the bears. But
Bears got that. I think that's a solid one.
My buddy Dylan is they got what they got the first round pick last year. They got a quarterback did
nothing buddy by the way. That was bro. I don't want to say, you know, we're gonna beat the fucking
ramps dude. That's easy. All I can say we can do it with like a little bet on the uh first week
They're causing me to see me my $20, but buddy by the way, I think you I think it's pretty sure
Will you do a private show for me if I send you some cash off tomorrow what?
Talk to who site
Okay, Bobby through Chris on this game like this one leaving the Raiders and Dolphins, bro
That's like let's see what's his name out of the new quarterback to work
Had to get used to these fucking headphones. I'm using bro. I gotta I feel like I gotta yell to hear anything because they know it's
Cancellation I can't even hear myself when I'm talking
No, you got drafted from fucking
Oh, yeah, yeah Mendoza, it's homophobic
Mendoza no doxon
I just say my last name dude. No, Noxon
Joe Joe shipply not drunk enough so he won't join he got to be put you know tipsy to come on
But what we've got a game tomorrow
So so Arthur what did uh, oh Arthur left?
4 p.m. Still isn't bills bills got it. I'll be back. I'll be back. I'll be back. Okay. Oh
Patriots and Browns Patriots
Niners and Raiders Niners
Rams and chargers fucking hate the Rams, but Rams you feel me commanders and Ravens
Ravens Falcons and Dolphins. I will leave out
Falcons you think so? Yeah
Texans and Panthers Texans
Bucks over Jags you're stripping giants over Jets. See that's where it gets jiggles over babbles easy. That was easy
Packers over Cardinals
Seahawks is well, they just want a superbowl of course you gotta pick the fucking Seahawks
And then, what?
Saints, cowboys.
Ooh, I'll leave those two alone.
Oh, I hate cowboys, too, though.
I don't even fuck cowboys.
Remember Broncos?
Broncos are Vikings all day.
Guys, you like dolphins?
You say you like the dolphins?
Lions and colts?
Lions.
Do you like the dolphins?
Bears and titans?
Bears.
The dolphins are playing.
Guys, you say you like dolphins?
Have a look.
Watch.
I think that's a rich ticket.
Let's go drop 10 on that.
Watch this.
I'll be like an 18, I'll pick 18 and I think I'm going to pick all of you.
I'll pick all of you, huh?
I'll pick all of you.
We got the slips, we can do it.
Jets over a giant.
The animal is abusing that moment.
Bucks, Texans.
Dad was over Vulcans.
That was rough.
Ravens.
Lambs over Tart.
Those are two Hortens, I think.
Rams, Niners, Patriots.
It's funny, it's because they train these dolphins
to jump up and do something.
Who's down to go?
People pay to have them.
Let's go put it in right now.
Well, uh, if you do it eight leg backs eight leg probably I don't know
I want these teams right now, so we have to lock in eight
Joe Joe come on up a panel
Oh, well
Listen
That's easy. I'm gonna just be what be
Over s because I'm gonna do that. I'm gonna be got the P over B Frank
If you know that, you know, if you know how to read that, yeah, what do you mean?
I can just look at this shouldn't be like, I know what the fuck it is.
Hey, I'll share the screen.
Psych, if you let me, I'll show you what we're looking at.
R over the C.
Okay.
Ravens over the C.
Oh, see, that looks good.
Two R's is going to keep the C's.
See that?
I'm leaving down with a one though.
That one's you, bro.
So this is preseason week.
You gotta think about third string, second string.
I think, you know, these are people
trying to make their spot, you know?
You don't get what you want to talk about. How was it listening? All of them. That's all it all is.
They're not using their fucking first string in the preseason. I mean, we got Josh Allen still in the build.
Yeah, he's not in preseason though. I promise you that. Why would you try to hurt him?
Like watching a shoe crime take place.
They're probably right. Exactly. Yeah, I'm trying to use you before I use my best name.
That's good input. So that will be, that might happen.
Yes, why would I use Josh Allen when I can use Matthew you might he might accidentally get hurt it preseason
We don't want that. We don't just hurt Matthews and Josh
I bet no, I'm just thought it's about the money. You know, it's about the championship. What does a good point?
You guys like watching wrestling you watch the WWE
Not really browns. I'm a Browns medal in the state a bronze medal wrestler. Yeah
Oh my god, oh my god
Yeah, this was 2012, though, on the road, texting to her.
Psyche, gay!
Bucks, hello, hello, hello, Jess, we have a bunch of gay people.
Talk to me, sir, we're the scary two Bucks over Gs, niggas, or the Jays.
I don't even want to bet on BJs.
They give me the BJs alone.
Hold on, Frank looks like a little brother of yours, Psyche.
I don't like that.
What the fuck is going on?
He's very uh, he's very good looking.
Well, I, you know, I have some dutch in me.
I like that dutch.
You know, he looks just like a little brother of yours.
Oh, thank you.
My ancestors died a horrible time.
Directly establishes the grudge.
I'm taking Packers over, Curtis.
Yo, this shit is crazy.
This little, like a little brother of yours.
That's crazy.
Packers over, uh, yeah.
I'm not saying that's a little bit of jealousy in there,
because I don't know you.
I think we should leave that alone.
I'm making sure.
I just need these seven of them right here.
Look at this YouTuber.
He's Frank.
And he's a Frank YouTuber.
Hey, Frank, your mic was a little low.
So how many?
We got one more because that's all I'm getting on.
You're OK?
Yeah.
Well, that's directly a good
Can you bring down Bobby's volume this guy's tongue
No Broncos Broncos
There you go. How's it going there chat Frank?
Greetings
What's up? I heard you're from what is it Belgium Netherlands?
Okay, well greetings. I am glad that the Netherlands did not win the World Cup
Well, we have saw me now
You're ready you're ready everything down, but if you write just the seven that you want to bet on I despise the Dutch
They should have never been in the World Cup final back in 2010 that should have been Uruguay
Uruguay was able to beat Spain
No, fuck the Dutch for life
I wasn't that you guys say it I can slide and slide and slide and I
Something that you're trying to prove because I'm just busting balls. I'm just busting balls
All right, I just like to push buttons
I guess you already ate dinner right I think you guys are like six seven hours ahead
Good job, you know time zones am I right though is it six hours seven hours like I said good job
You know time zones. All right, this guy wants to be a smart as now see all right hold on
Good job, you know time zones. All right, so all right
I think you're a little straight edge your little brother here
I think the chat's got enough of him.
The guy next wants to use a clap coin on him, too.
OK, why are you guys not here and you don't have a clap coin?
It's like a pile up.
You're snacking in there.
Patriots.
Of course.
I'm not going to use a clap coin.
So, yeah, so I just want to explain, Frank had a true crime show, a successful one, and then he threw it all away, and he restarted it from time to time.
I'm starting over.
Interesting.
So I apologize if your pillars of hierarchy doesn't give me, like, it doesn't really rattle me.
Yes, I am one of the higher ups here, and I approve of your presence here.
He's higher up.
I guess he's right under B, though, right?
Right, right, right under, right under.
Right under, right?
Right there.
We actually don't approve of smoking. So I think it seems like he's smoking right now. All right. Well, that's definitely a negative
No, that's a negative
you know, cash up. Well, I want to show you, Frank, a true crime video, and I'm sure it's a short thing, and I think it's been a true crime and stuff, but I'm going to see.
Yeah.
You're welcome to, you know.
This is my friend.
I'm off today, bro.
You know, I'm not going to walk right now.
What was that big block on that side of it?
We got a ride.
I don't even want to drive.
Hey, Sike, bro, like fuck me.
Yeah.
Can you give us a ride real quick?
Yeah, I'll give you a ride. Come get in my car.
You give us a ride.
I'm not a fan of Frank at all.
You gotta be honest.
No, I'm good.
Blows of claim currently circulating online that creator Alexandra mayors launched a vicious
unsubstantiated slander campaign against two other creators psyche and inks
The supposed basis for this attack is a live stream with an undeniably ominous title
Alexandra mayors live
Utah politics how a PDF led to the closure. It sounds like a digital smoking gun
online allegations function as social currency a 10-second
4-hour stream
I don't think he's interested in that's like
No, but he said he quit that so I don't think he's really interesting
It's all right, we could do without him, you know what I mean
Okay
We don't need a mirror
He looks like a little brother yours
I'm not sharing a channel. He was so rude in his like laugh. I mean, it's called like Frank Frank's prime analysis
Frank prime analysis
And the second time he did it the first time he said I was like when I played the clip of like be pretending to be sweet
P on good times. He said I was like I was committing a crime
impersonating somebody
So so so so Bobby viewer wrestler. Oh, yes, sir, okay
We left out one too
Okay, we need like seven
Roddy got mine with one two three
four five six seven eight nine ten
Yeah, so I'm down to wrestle with you guys
Of course
Yeah, no
Check it like a baby fool
Okay, I won't I won't against you
I don't know why you keep trying to pick them, bro, leave them two alone as well.
All right.
Bro, those two are stupid.
I used to be a sports betting.
I used to be a sports betting as well.
Texans.
Okay, that one's easy.
Texas over Panther.
I know.
I want to gain 40 pounds.
Okay, so Carl's back.
So Carl wants to talk to you again.
I left that one alone too.
You really picking the giants over the Jets?
You just remind me
Am I on right now
All right, all right, so so okay, so clumsy is right here in chat. Okay, so
Okay, okay, so clumsy has a bears
Chris K has the egos Bobby has the 49ers. I had their Rams. We're all betting 20 bucks
Who's gonna have the best season not but not play ourselves just a regular season?
So somebody's gonna win 60 bucks at the end of the season. That's all
We're not we're not going to play a bro. No playoffs. Yeah, it's a regular season. Yeah, no playoffs. Yeah
Yeah
Yeah, no, no, just
Numbers went with Chris K. It was in losses
No, Chris K really wins and losses who has a better season. Is it the Eagles?
Is it the 49ers? Is it the Rams or the Bears?
Honestly, honestly, honestly when it comes down to it honestly to be honest with you guys
I think it's gonna come down to with the Bears and the Rams
Honest, yeah
The Eagles at 49ers soft dude
They're not gonna do anything big during the regular season. Remember no playoffs. This is regular season
Remember we all remember remember clumsy clumsy right there in chat. We all agree to this
And and me and clumsy also better
No, no, he's we know he left a lion
No, he left the lines to the ramps and also to it was a core a core of back swap
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, and also to
Tomsy and I have a bet to on this side who's gonna have a better season the Bears or the Rams because
It comes he brought it up and a Chris gay I'll tell you now who went to the playoffs last year
Remember when the Rams played that when they went to the fucking Chicago and they played the Bears
That was a good fucking game. Remember that Chris gay. Did you bet on that shit?
No, no, no the Rams beat the Bears
Dear tweaking bro chill out dude chill out
Yeah, yeah, exactly. Yeah, they did they did but that was that was that was the next round. Yes. Yes
But Chris Cato remember that one game in Chicago last year with the Rams and Bears that kid and went either way no homo
Right
Bro the Bears are coming up, bro. The Bears are coming up
In all phases in all phases. So that's when I wanted to bet clumsy and I'm a man of my word and so is he
You know what's funny man the Rams went to the championship the last two years
Yeah, the first game the first game of a preseason
They're not gonna fucking play their the main quarterbacks, right, of course not of course not yeah
Yeah
Who is this Nick? What's up, Nick?
Are you doing Nick? Hey, bro, what's up a long time no see man?
Nick Nick is neutral. What's up, Nick? How you doing, bro? I know time to see man
No, Nick, do you want to get in this you wouldn't you wouldn't bet or what?
Are you a football fan, do you have it like a special team away?
I mean, yeah, I guess the cowboys, but we suck. Oh
Shit the cowboy the cowboys man. That's that's one of my nephews teams. I have many nephews listen
Maybe you can get into this man. You can get in this baby. Hey
No, hey Chris Chris Chris a clumsy Bobby weeks are bringing in because this season hasn't started yet
So if you want started
It don't matter it don't matter
It don't matter
Hey a clumsy a clumsy so the moon chat listen Chris K Bobby we can bring him in and just bet two
Who's gonna have the better season? Are you are you with that?
was in 20 and take all the money. Nick, are you with that? Nick? Oh, no, you don't know.
Wait, was it like the cowgirls? Is that what he said? Okay. Christian, you're funny.
I gave up on football because the cowboy is a cowboy. He got the Dallas stars. But any
given a but Nick, though, any given Sunday and and the Cowboys have potential. They do.
They do. Hey, stop. You're doxxing. Stop doxxing.
out my boy hold on let's stop doxing dude we can't we can't you follow me Chris he just
doxed him dude son of a bitch everybody kind of knows you're already from around here more
or less yeah no nick is cool as fuck dude yeah all right so okay so we got that four
Me
No, it's only four of us right now
There you go, there's four there's four is Bobby is Bobby Chris K myself and clumsy
There's a four-way bet.
Somebody at the end of the season is going to make 60 bucks.
I get like a bookie fee because I'm here doing it on my show.
OK, now, Sike, do you have a team?
Do you want to get in this or what?
Yeah, I want to get out of this.
So who is, what's the?
OK, so it's a simple bet, Sike.
Who's going to have the better season?
No playoffs.
I like white pants. What color pants?
Well, a lot of them wear white pants.
And then you can see the jockstress.
Well, you can see that with all of them. Yeah.
Well, but the white pants.
Everybody's got a pair of white pants.
There you go. There you go, Nick. Yeah.
So who has the white pants?
Everybody one week then one color
I'm serious about this bit I mean these these two these two
Freight to choose for me Frank choose me a team
Bobby Bobby choose me a team to bet Bobby choose me a team
But it's a it's as simple as it and fighting bet right Chris K. It's only 20
Right Chris K. Hey, bro, it's only it's a it's a cool bet
Well that I we can't have that we can't have that dude. We can't have that
Somebody's gonna somebody I make up the month because he's got one more weekend this season
Like they a Chris K. Honestly, bro, that'd be cool. We bring it to more people because at the end of the season
Someone's gonna win a hundred bucks. Yeah, it'd be cool. Let me
Yeah, it's only 20 bucks, it's a fun it's a fun bet. No
I'm not tripping. I'm not chicken
Chris K. Chris K. Chris K. Chris K. If you remember I'm the one who started this bet, right?
Right Christian, I'm the one
So
All right, so I get but you're not putting anything into it how you're gonna win
I understand that I understand that yes
Okay, I understand that but you're not putting anything into this bet though
Pick a pick a team pick a team and run with that
Sackie pick a team around with it. Oh, he said office. Okay. Okay. So everybody heard okay. Hey Chris K
Oh, he said office of all the teams you're gonna lose bro. You're gonna lose
Okay Broncos. Oh, oh, he said oh, he said Broncos Chris K. No, we got sucky. He said Broncos
What where's clumsy at where's clumsy at clumsy was there a check all right Chris K Chris K
Chris K mark it down the psyche is with the Broncos
You get a mark it down dude
Mark it down with the date today the 26 thumbs. I'm sorry Chris K, please
You gotta write it down, bro
You get ready down
Yeah, or do right there bro. Okay, so we all you know our teams right and now psyche is with with the Broncos
The psyche is in 20 bucks. Let's go
So whoever loses okay cool whoever winner now they're gonna win 80 bucks
Let's get one more person. So at the end of the season someone's win a hundred bucks. Let's go
Let's go Chris K
Put the date bro. You got to put the date to
Because because we got it. We got it. We got to solidify what psyche to say he's with the Broncos
Chill out homeboy chill out. He's gonna put the date a 26 26
You're a day ahead homeboy today's a 26
All right, all right, so Nick you want to get in this or what Nick it's only 20 bucks
So Nick you can you can lose 20 bucks or you can win a hundred bucks. How about that?
Yeah, he's with the Broncos pay attention
You buy your shit
Sockies with the Broncos and put the date down
Chris game
This was the collage. I made 27 years. Yeah. Yeah, Nick. That's cool. Fuck bro. So Nick you want in this or what with the cowboys?
Listen bro, you can either you can either lose 20 bucks or you can win a hundred bucks
That was 27 years old today
Those are pretty good odds
No favorite movie
There was so great with the cheeks, and raiders start sucking you, it was so hard, bro.
I
Favorite song want to be a ball or
There's Sam and right there. Hey Sam and you're trying to get at Mimi, huh? You think you're gonna take Mimi get her get her
Come on, Sam and get a get a Mimi. Oh, she wants you so bad. She wants you so bad
Sam and she's waiting for you Sam and she's Sam and she's waiting for you. She wants you so bad
Yeah, yeah, she she wants you so bad Sam and she's waiting for you to sweepers sweep off her feet out there in New York
She blocked you she still has a block they get past that block
You fucking incel. You're a fucking incel, Sam. You're a fucking incel.
Yeah, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man, man
That that's actually that's actually good odds
Hey, hey Sam that talk about Mimi again talk about how you're gonna get her she's single right she's single, huh?
She loves you, huh? Right Sam, but she still has you blocked right, but you wouldn't be with her
You you and you and your fucking weirdo brother, right?
Honestly, what happened? What happened? What happened? What happened with that? What do you knew you what do you knew your girls, huh?
What happened saman
Get the fuck out of here, dude
Damn right she's from the Bronx. Yeah, that's my lady. That's my ruka. That's my right or die
damn right
Just saw her today behind the scenes
Do I have to prove that I talk to her due to this community fuck this community
She's not with me but we're talking about having a kid later on right right right salmon right salmon
We talk about when we get married and we might have a kid, but she's not with me, right?
Right, Saman? Right, Saman?
Right, Saman?
Saman, she still has you blocked there, right?
But you're trying to get her hurt
How are you gonna Saman? How are you gonna Sam it shut up tweaker? How are you gonna circumvent that?
How are you gonna get around that Saman?
See, Carl wants to come in this bitch talking shit with his bitch ass.
How are you going to get her, Samman?
How are you going to get her?
Well, how are you going to get anything that you got?
We were talking about marriage and having a kid, but yet, what are you going to provide
for her?
She's coming out today.
She's coming out to SoCal.
I have a house ready the next few months, Samman.
She's going to live with me.
I will take care of her.
What can you provide for her, Samman?
That weird food that used to show on fucking your your your server on this
What are you gonna provide what are you gonna provide for salmon what you're gonna lie you're gonna lie to everyone say that you
Met a brother like you did with KK, right?
What are you gonna do? What are you gonna do salmon?
You can lie about me but Mimi like you do with KK
You fucking weirdo. Hey, Sam, you are the epitome of a fucking in-solder
Hey
Spin sauce one boy who spins
All to be talking that crazy
Spin size dude spin size
Hey
I
Can't be that old because of I lose I gotta I gotta pay up the bet right you want me to croak before I pay up the
Bet you want that 20 bucks for the year for your for your speed homeboy, right?
For your glass for your glass
No, you don't want me to croak before that before the bet ends
No, you don't want me to croak before the bet ends
you need that money for your drugs homeboy chill out chill out homeboy chill out
damn chris k this year a fuckboy right here chris k this year this is this year this year a
fuckboy right here chris k damn no i could dish it out and i could take about there's nothing
I can dish it all out and nothing come back my way home boy
The same as in chat
You're a clown because you don't know saying that you're more of a clown honestly you're
more of a clown yeah imagine you imagine right for some of you know well thank you that's
actually a compliment because I like pretty good from age thank you
Thank you. That's actually a compliment. It's done. It does. That's a compliment. Thank you. Oh boy. What else?
Yeah, he actually complimented me you dumb fuck
So psyche are you serious about this bet psyche so you got you got the process
Yes, okay. Okay. So Chris K. Okay. Okay. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
Morals by the way morals in this community shut that fuck up dude
You can't even give a little bit of something to even appreciate anything
All right, whatever. No doubt that was psyche you dumbass listen. This is Carl. Hey Chris okay, Chris K
Chris Chris did you put down?
Chris Chris Chris
Chris
Calm down calm down your trick right there calm down your trick. Hey, hey Chris. Did you put down that psyche is what the Broncos?
What do you what do you got Chris? What do you got bro you got Q 49ers Carl Ram's
Let's go. Let's go. So let's see if we can get one
So, let's see let's see if we can get one one more person
No, no, no, no, no, no, we can get one more one more person. We like to represent different teams, right?
So a so Chris K that's this is this like a cool bet. You know, I mean 20 bucks boys
So we can win 80 or even a hundred bucks
Because wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I guess the Rams at 49ers
Well, I hate the 49ers soon
No, no preseason regular season Chris K. What the fuck dude
Okay, okay, how about this? How about this Bobby? How about this listen to me? Bobby Bobby?
Bobby
Okay, I read Bobby stop tweaking listen to me listen to me Chris K. I
Bet Chris K. I bet clumsy on the side, right?
No, no, I'm not Chris K Chris K. Yeah, I bet I Chris K
Get you get your get your girl
Chris K
Put a sock in it put a sock in it. Okay. Listen Chris K. So me and clumsy bet on the Rams versus
Bears who's gonna have a better season on the side
On the side
So so Chris K your homeboy is tweaking right now. So maybe he wants it bet
the Rams versus 49ers he's gonna have a better season season not not postseason regular season
does he want to bet that chris k i'm still with that i want to as he chris k as he go for his word
chris k so you want it like uh on the side you want to bet more than 20 no but i'm asking yeah but
i'm asking you chris k you know him for how long you can vouch for him he's good for his word
Yeah. Yeah. I can. Yeah.
I'm watching. I'm watching.
I can barely feed me my bitch with that with two burritos or the extra cheese in me.
Can't eat a lot.
That's what I like.
Dude.
What?
A little bit in the mouth.
Yeah, a little bit in the mouth.
Yeah.
What?
Fuck the eagle.
That's what I'm talking about.
He burnt them up.
You know
Fuck him I will fucking put a referee shirt on and I will fuck him up
And then I'll run off and he'll think the referee did it
What Roger good
Hey, what is this? What is that in a hockey team the stars? Yeah, that's Dallas
I like to
He's in Texas. Hey, I don't know about hockey man. That's why I'm asking you.
You don't know hockey? You're white as fuck!
Black as fuck, everyone!
You got Mike McDonald.
Look up to your Mike McDonald career clip.
You watch up Mike McDonald.
Andy Mogue.
Garcy Wappamot.
The hockey is the only sport that has been squabbled.
Oh, that was a nice one.
I was big on the goalie. I think as a kid with one of the kids on the street had a goal that I wanted to buy
And I would always play
I guess I'm done with this
I already know everybody's I'm not going to get shit on my desktop. So what's five times 20?
Honey, honey, bro, come on
Well, then I only put 20 in it and I'm taking 80 from all units.
Add more, bro.
That's what's up.
What?
I need some base in my card.
Well, when somebody comes in and say, like, I got the Cowboys, that's an easy 20.
Cowboys?
Easy 20.
I gave only a good team.
Broncos is good.
I did not cheat.
I think the Broncos might beat the Rams.
49ers.
Rams is the least.
I'm risking the Eagles right now because I really, I don't know how they're going to
play right now.
I don't know about the Eagles either.
I'm risking it.
I do feel for Jalen Herrington shit and Saquon and all that, but
If you feel bitter bad
You feel me?
You think he's got some competition
And your division is stupid
So I already know 20 bucks, you know, over the hours
Fuck 20 dollars
That shit
I don't drink that shit in an hour
Bro, who's in the party, bro?
Did the gay homie leave?
He's backstage or some shit
I'm not gonna lie, Carl's a little gay
I think Carl's hella gay. I mean, yeah, that's weird. You can't be too. I mean, I get it. You old, but you gotta be cool and old. You can't just be lame and old. Like, bro, you just ask backwards. He's reverse reverse. I mean, if you all at least try to be cool.
You guys are leaving me, don't leave me, hey I want some private time with Bobby on
Discord.
What happened?
I want some time with you on Discord.
I'll cover your back.
Bro, I just don't want to talk to Carl
Hey, he fucked up two times already, bro, like he's I hate niggas that's too negative like making life sucks
Like it's good, bro. Like chill out like nobody's like happy all the time like we did but don't come over here trying to ruin
I don't know what the fuck happening in your life in your household. Did you say good morning? Good night to somebody?
You didn't get no pushes this morning. What happened, bro?
Stupid.
But you get a lot to see, huh?
Yeah, I'm a fucking people's person.
I hate niggas that are all impressive.
Because then when niggas go and get aggressive,
do you want to go to the place I want to go?
I actually don't want to go there, but we can go there.
You know what I'm saying?
Yeah.
You're not meeting where I want to go.
You're not matching nothing.
Yeah.
Because we're talking online with each other, bro. Just be nice. Well, I can never touch you
Well, if you ever want to come through
Don't mess niggas. I'm right here in the ghetto. Pull them up, bro
MTV walkthrough we'll show my crib where we live
show them where all the, where all the druggies are,
where the fentanyl's at, where everybody overdoses.
I like, I like our own live stream, right?
Is what I'm talking about, outside the shit?
Yeah, I don't know nothing, bro.
They're probably in the suburbs and shit.
I was telling you, I tell you, like,
we're gonna do some, uh, shit we can do it right now,
but, uh, I got to go.
It's too hot, man, I'm not burning.
Actually, yeah.
You got me before.
I think I'm gonna shut it.
Cause it, you know, we're, you know.
Yeah, we're doing it.
It's a hundred and what?
It's a hundred and ten.
Yeah, it's literally, yeah, it's gonna go up.
It wasn't going to go down, it doesn't get higher in there.
Like some day it will, but nigga.
Look at it, it's gonna probably go to 111, like by five.
You think so?
Yeah.
It's stupid, hell no.
It goes lower, nigga.
Well, look, we get beautiful.
We gotta wait till fucking Saturday.
Hey, September, bro, I told you.
That's not even September, Saturday is not September.
June, July, August, three months.
No, I'm just saying, Saturday is not September though.
I think Saturday is still fucking August.
Saturday is still August, it's 29th.
So a couple days, how many days?
It's gonna be beautiful in September though.
Whoa, for the word it showed me.
As I said, like June, July, August is like fucking hell
in Vegas, but after that,
I
Want to get out of here
I have it has been this is the hottest August ever in Vegas this fucking this
August that we're we're you guys wearing so many clothes
you should be like you know
she said it's too hot get undressed this is the new gay
this is all good it's like you
hey how about I'm gonna bring a woman inside
I'll bring you a woman here I'll bring a less gay there's a woman here
hey psyche
actually at this point it's pretty normal
hey Chris K
yo yo
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Sam-Man's a f***ing plat me, ain't he?
Yeah.
He was talking on the floor and he plays Yu-Yu with kids and sh**t.
Yeah, he's a predator.
What's fine with his brothers or is he like family or is he like random ass kids?
I don't know, I heard he has a brother, but I'm not sure.
I know he's a f***ing loser.
He's like almost 50 years old and he lives in section 8.
Who the f*** is that old of this b***h?
Yeah, he lives in section eight.
I'm gonna be old eventually.
He's fucking he lives on food stamps and she's fucking
That's that's me these people that run these streams like Samman, you know, don't say
That man thinks he's hard, but he don't run all day. Listen all day
He's a fucking loser
And guess what? He's like he's like 600 pounds. Can you imagine like being on here like you know fucking?
Well, tell them to give me a hundred. From the time you wake up you get on me
I don't know what's going on, bro.
Yeah.
This shit, bro.
You want to do the bit?
I got it going.
I got it.
this is the uh it's a psyche show and we are his dancing monkeys
i am a monkey it's okay i don't think we're all his dancing monkeys
i would have a dancing monkey too but he's i think i'm i think i was made from a monkey
I think I was made from an orange tangerine, or the middle with the red butt cheek, you think?
Yeah, I like it.
I like it.
We want to come.
Dude, this is strong.
This should be.
Hey, don't throw it.
If you don't, if you don't.
Oh, chill out, chill out.
I don't mind throwing it out.
Set it aside.
Please don't throw it away.
I like it.
Zen?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
You know.
You're gonna pick those.
What is that what he does and you already you already made it. Oh, stop being pussy on the stream
Psychi
Psychi with you on the crack here cuz I'm gonna stream with you in some motion and all I do is drink
Thank you, this guy looks like the team version of Jude Bellingham. Oh, I'll take it. Is that you?
There and I'm talking about you look up Jude look up Jude Bellingham
Look it up look it up
There you go
Let me sit this
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know. I don't know. I
don't know. I don't know. I
Yeah
Hey team over not I'm still a dick is still better by me
They caught will you a trigger nigga, I'm not
Probably like a draggy version. You're not a trigger. I don't know what what you be doing over here. Can I defend you or not?
I can't
Have a question I have a question. So your friend. What do you think of this picture here?
Listen, that's a pretty woman
I'm transitioning into a fucking Puerto Rican woman. Okay, so let me check you out. Oh, that's that's like that's a man
No, it's psyche sister
That bitch gay. That's the beer. Why are you guys being mean?
It's fucking
if you got a coochie, I'm going to bang that bitch.
If she show me a dick, I'm going to slap that bitch.
There you go, psyche.
The dick will be put up in a thong.
And then there's a booty hose available, I guess.
Booty hose.
OK.
Compromise?
That sounds like a perfect compromise.
You compromise?
You put that shit in that tweeter bitch, didn't you, bro?
You put it in the ass.
You gave me it.
What you think
Somebody in the chat said tell the brown one to take his shirt off show those dark nipples
No, not you he's talking about what's your name Bobby
Bobby just like just whatever you want somebody you somebody wants to see your your chocolate nipples
Yeah, the ladies in the chat the ladies in the chat, let me see put it on tell her how old
Tell her she gotta convince me. I can't just do shit.
Ray, can you convince him please? Ray, please, for me.
What's her? Oh, Ray? Oh, I'm not fucking with Ray.
She's been disrespected for a while now.
I- uh, no, I just-
Now I haven't even made a stoppage.
It's different, Ray.
Oh, no.
I just- I just like to push buttons, okay? That's it. That's it.
I'm not fucking with Ray.
I brought him to this, to the you guys.
I brought you to this.
Ryan, go ahead and say something, Ryan.
You're talking.
No, like, you know, I also like to push Chris Kay's buttons, too.
You know?
Yeah, you can't throw my buttons.
I ain't even wearing no buttons.
You know what I'm saying?
There is no button when you don't push.
Actually, I'm AI now, I'm like touchscreen, you gotta like fingerprint, finger scan, I need thumbtack, I need face scan, you know what I'm
I'm elevated, you feel me, I need more than a fucking button.
Are you the FBI or what?
Time shit, go ahead and pick it up.
Give it all to you. What's your my chart? I need it all. Oh, you don't need to know that
Like you want to see your tattoo
I want to see your um your tattooless body. Well, no, listen, that's why I don't want to take my shirt off, bro
You know, I got I got I want to see here. I want to see your white supremacist
Chris K, you don't have any chest tattoos
You need to line get some edges
Chris K, you don't have any chest tattoos. Take off your shirt for one second
I don't you know, I don't want to you know, I'm trying to like I want to see it. I want to see it
I've been embarrassed trying to be cool. Did you blubbering as fuck?
Come on Chris, do it.
That's not what I'm talking about.
Don't embarrass yourself.
Chris doesn't want to show anybody his tits.
Can Bobby do it or are you guys just too shy?
The fruits.
He has pepperoni nipples.
I want to see Bobby's brown nipples.
I want to see if there's hair on them.
I want to see all kinds of things.
Yeah, oh, yeah, we see that show tits
No, no, we're talking
That was I mean, I need more of you girl
That was psyche. I'll show you my my daughter's bill. I need more of you. You gotta entice me
Hey, shoot a fucking, you know, uh five bucks cash out. Whoa. Whoa. All right, and Chris K shows his pepperoni nipples
I don't need no money for these nipples.
Why are you trying to get some money for these?
Actually, $5, you think my nipples were $5 bucks?
You would whore yourself for $5, Chris.
For cash up, I want to see his asshole.
I would never.
I'm not even trying to show myself right now.
Stupid.
I would be mad if you showed yourself.
And you probably showed yourself for nothing.
I don't show myself to anybody.
Don't piss me off.
Have you ever dated a stripper Bobby?
I'm in love with a stripper
You'll be mine nowadays
What is it, what's the song?
Can we help you with this?
Well I'm like the stage's like 60, 70 man
And frankly, all this
This bitch Liar
He's calling you a Liar
Psyche
Do you guys ever do booby bumps?
Have you heard of a booby bump?
How many booby baddies you got?
I don't have baby daddies. I don't have babies.
Yeah. Share my others. Share my others.
I don't have babies. I only have kids.
Nope.
Okay. I just thought I could play with that.
Don't you open up that way, girl.
I can't play that much of the song.
She's talking to one of you.
Like a middle-aged listener.
But you can sing it, Chris.
Yeah. Sing it, Chris.
And then take off your shirt while you do that.
I don't have kids. I'm only 27 weirdo. I'm only 29. What does that mean?
You have kids? Shit. I know people who had kids at 1560. What do you mean? What does 27 mean?
What? How many kids do you have, sir?
Alright, 60. Oh my god. You're such a whore.
You're a whore.
I got two.
I told you baby King.
Other people agree.
You're two. That's cool.
That's just slut you are.
I was with my bitch for 13 years.
Stop playing.
I just love sluts.
You make it loud.
You bitches are real lords.
Fuck strippers or what?
Fuck!
This is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this is what it is, this
My bitch weren't at the shit club stupid. Yeah, he's the one that like
doesn't have shit for a round.
You know how I be filming that night when I gotta pick her up?
Is she even clapping ass or a hell of a dick?
Well, when you see the face you should have fun with money.
If you want, put the beers in the trash.
Is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one, is this one
You're my content right now.
Hey, how many views we got right now?
It's like, 48 people in chat.
You guys are like stars.
Oh, we were down.
We were down a little bit, but maybe take off your shirts
so we can get more people in here.
That's because you need to chill.
No, I mean, yeah.
Chris, take off your shirt.
I want you to see Chris's tattoos.
Yeah, take off your shirt, Chris.
Yeah, I don't know what I like to wear on your arm.
Chris, what's up?
I don't know.
Fuck this song.
This song's gay.
Yeah, I'm dancing with you.
I mean, that's good.
Oh my gosh, boy Carl. Oh my gosh, okay for five more minutes of you and then I'm just left on your own
I'm having a normal conversation
No, am I online can you hear me? Yes, I'm a lady
I can stay in whatever the fuck I want wait wait wait
Yes, how do you always put the rain in rain? No
Carlos, he's still getting this. He's still in here
Yeah, yeah, I'll kick your bucket rain. Can you hear me? No? Oh my gosh
Yes, you hear me. Hey Chris. So you got that jotted down bros for their bets. Let's go
Wait, that's okay. What's up, dog? What?
So you gotta draw it down for the bets. That's why I'm that's I'm coming back. Oh, yeah
Hey, it's like you kick me really man. I'm on bets. Yeah
I'm sorry rain. No, not though. Those are all those are all
Either way down there was pretty chill out
We all owe money off of this ticket and psyche, psyche Broncos proper. Yeah, did you put it down anybody else to join?
That's what I'm saying, bro. Before the season starts, let's go. That's okay.
Hey, rain, how's it going?
I got the list.
No, that's wrong.
The brain are you still there? No shit. She left. That's
Yeah, I don't know what you I don't know what you're showing that that's
Real ticket by the way
But that's not our bet though, okay our bets only five teams bro, and it says a Q 49ers Carl Ram
Clums bears Chris Eagles psych is Broncos. That's all we get
Yeah
Shut up. This is $10 on my 10 team. Hey, this has nothing to do with you
That's what I'm saying though that has nothing to do with our with our bet though or with our current bet
Okay, I already said your bets over here
You don't even have my energy
Chris can you hear me? Yes
I'm gonna say man, we can get one more person if we get one more person
Then that'd be great man. Was it if we can get one more person that'd be great
What Nick what Nick likes to kill boys Nick
No, bro, he'll pay up dude, he'll pay up
But he might win though too. He might win though. He might win, you know
But I'll put the dolphins over all our teams if you think he's gonna win
I'm gonna say a man like they said a give a Sunday any given any given season man. Hey Chris K
Hey, Chris K. Hey, bro. Chris K. You know how it works, man
Chris K any give a Sunday any given season man. Sometimes these teams fucking come out of nowhere
Don't you ever say
I just the son. Oh my god son. Don't you ever say that's bothering me bearded. That's you
I crushed my shit.
Are you crushing anything?
Saki, where are you at, man?
What are you doing?
I'm right here watching this.
Saki's at home on this business day.
OK, OK.
But Saki, that's cool when you're coming in there.
So Saki, you're putting in $20, you can lose $20,
or you can win $80.
We're just trying to get one more person.
One more person, Saki, so we can get 100.
So we can put in 20, some at the end of the season.
could win 100 bucks.
Yeah, we need an easy 20, dude.
Somebody in chat or whatever you want to like, you know.
Let's go, Nick.
With your cowboys.
Come on, Nick.
Hey, watch this shit happen.
You're not going to be here.
Somebody is going to buy some flat points.
I'll sell it.
Excuse me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bobby, chill out, tweaker.
I'm sorry.
Psyche, what did you say?
I'll sell us a flat point for the $20.
Shut up, fucking shit.
Mute this, fucker.
I'm sorry.
What's your business?
I can't even hear.
I can't even hear fucking Psyche.
I don't want you to hear shit. How about that?
Shoot, shoot, shoot it for me.
Mute it up, dude. Mute this fucking fucking shit, bro.
Mute this tweaker, dude.
I'm not even a party talking shit.
Let it finish the sits.
Go ahead.
I said, I'll sell five clap tokens for $20
if somebody wants to buy it,
and then I'll put that towards that,
that bet, whoever it is, it was Bobby or whatever.
Okay, okay
Okay, okay, okay, but psyche we're talking about the best change something we got to wait till the end of the season
But you a demo address Chris K. Hey, bro, you don't know about throughout the season man
We're gonna be fucking showing each other man. Who's good better. He's doing less. You know, I mean, yeah
I mean, like I said, the Eagles, I don't even know, like, you know,
they could be good or bad.
So I'm taking a risk.
I'm taking a risk.
I don't know what anything is going to happen.
I don't know how.
Shut the fuck up.
They're like the top five team, dude.
Shut the fuck up, dude.
Right, top three team.
Thank you.
But anyway, so.
But yet, like I was telling Chris earlier, any game of Sunday,
any game of season, right?
That's the top five and we're betting on five teams
49ers of the fun is are definitely top five. Yeah, they are hell. Yeah, they are
Yeah, that's why I'm getting
Chris let's go all our teams right now. Listen everybody right now betting psyche pay attention
This guy keeps talking all these teams all these teams are top five or top ten
All the betters that we get us like that's what there's one and there is no we need we need we need a Seahawks fan
Do you come in this shit? We need a Seahawks fan become this shit
I forget what we need a Seahawks fan to come in this shit 20 bucks. Exactly, but I wasn't gonna give sight Seahawks
Anybody from the chat a year Seahawks fan come in this shit put in 20 bucks. You put in 20 bucks
You can lose 20 bucks
Oh
come on Chris dude hey Chris you guys better for for right now the Rams are
gonna take this it hey clumsy and psyche all you guys bear for free because the
Rams gonna take the regular season let's go I mean you know we don't believe
what the fuck he said we got no the Chargers are in there nobody picked
me no Chargers no Chris I say the Seahawks Seahawks that's your problem
Not my problem. I'm with the Rams homeboy. The fuck is the same division homeboy true
But I'm going to Rams
We we Bobby you and I are in the same division fuck the point
Fuck the 49ers dude
Appropriate if there was anybody watching that has family that don't hear that
Come on
But you see there was like a some highlight right there you click the button and fucking made it up
Which out now we're good. No, it's that there is family came back
At the night show
So it's like you feel good about the Broncos
Like that's a good team for you, right?
OK, brother, I'm not Bobby.
Shut up.
Tweaker.
Sike doesn't know nothing about football.
Yes, it does.
Let him talk.
Sike.
So you feel good about the broke up yell at me.
I mean, I want to see a picture of Bobby.
And as you know, oh my gosh, sir.
Sike, listen, last year, this year,
I want to see the wrestling videos.
Hey, how many how many games for the regular season?
It's like 17 now.
Okay, so let's see what what do you think the Rams are going to do? Nothing. Oh 15 and 2 easy
Let's go
Let's go. Let's go chris. Come on chris. Come on chris. I just
So what do you think ego is going to do?
Come on Chris be honest
All right Chris K put that next to my name right there put that 15 and 2
Man, wait, but if you didn't get the fuck out of here, dude, you're tweaker
You're gonna be zero and 17 to fuck the 49ers dude
So what do you think?
Right, right, right, you know, I'm not worried about the
Jesus Christ dude chill out homeboy. You didn't watch last year. Huh?
Patriots nobody can say Patriots Patriots. I'm gonna say Eagles Eagles 11 and 6
Okay, okay, that's that's conservative. I get that. Okay, put it down put it down Chris. Put it down
Tap that shit in dude. What do you got?
Chris are you top that shit in on your laptop?
Very competing. Yeah, I'm like I would have a 14 a text document
Okay, we'll put in I say 15 and 2 with the Rams you say 11 6 11 6 with your
Homeboy that's what you mean is going to get all these numbers
Okay, okay, I'll see okay the Seahawks and the 49ers
And I'm giving him the same thing at home at home too
The Rams lose at home against against their fucking rifles. They lose at home dude. They do
That's like that's super high 15 and 2 for the Rams
Let's fucking go Chris
Come on Chris
Let's go. I got 11 and six you got what?
Okay, let's just psyche. Okay psyche. Okay psyche now 17 games psyche how many games do you think that the egos are gonna win
17 17
Fucking tweaker you said it wrong stupid
Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay.
Okay. All right. Saki. How many
games do you think Alice 17 that
the Broncos will win? Thank you.
You said a nice six. There you go.
You said six. What you're going to
lose, bro.
9 he doesn't know shit about football dude
He said 13 he said 13
Yeah
What the fuck is happening?
Bro Chris K. Do people don't know what they're fucking Betty here. What the fuck
Bobby Bobby, what do you think the record?
All right, Bobby a tweaker. Hey Bobby, what do you think the 49ers are gonna end this season with what?
Yeah
You said 14-3 oh
14-3 oh
Oh shit and here you go Nick now. What do you think about the Cowboys?
Oh, come on come on Nick get in this bro. You're the last you're the last one getting this with 20 bucks
Dude, but it's when it was you lose 20 bucks or win a hundred bucks. How about that? Oh, yeah
Nick you want to get this right now
Nick yeah or nay
Yeah
Yes, I highlighted all the chat
Yes, or no
Nick I don't understand what you're saying to say yes or no
Let him talk to let him talk
No, he's okay. There you go. That's a fifth one now. There you go. Now Nick Nick right there. Say he's going to Cowboys
Yes, okay, put it in put it in Chris K
Cowboy
This game put it in Nick from Cowboys. Well, I mean, what's his the is the name of Nick Nick? What Nick just just put it Nick
Remember cuz I'm not gonna remember this guy. We all know Nick
I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I'm a new person. I
Everybody okay, there's five of us now. Okay, there's five men. We're betting you put in 20 bucks
You can lose 20 bucks or you can win a hundred bucks at the end of the season at the regular season Nick regular season
Let's go
Damn, Nick, you better fuck right now. They can't play suck. They can't play suck dude
I'm gonna say Nick
Damn Nick really
Nick you should have picked the Patriots even though we don't like it
Fuck
World tour by the way, where where am I I get a homeboy I can show them on my own channel where am I no world tour
I can't even say which one.
Can you guys chill out home girl?
Listen, I know you're back in the day, just chill out, okay?
Can you guys see no Carl?
Are you friends with him back there?
No, she knows me all right, yeah.
We go way back from Captain Content, Faggot, Shimmer.
Hey, Carl!
Carl!
What, Faggot?
No, I feel is what you bro. You're cool as fuck nigga, but just don't be no
Bro just banter bro come on chill out dude. It's just banter
You but you're tweaking as fuck dude you're tweaker dude chill out chill out really hot. I don't know what you get nations from but look
Yeah, cheers bruh cheers
Virtual virtual cheers you faggot
All right, Chris K. So we got five
Let's go Chris K. Now we got a five
Sight if you fucking me to cry for a second put them on backstage we need clumsy we need clumsies
No one cares about views like fuck you man, I don't want to be famous
Right based on the fucking paparazzi, you know
They're gonna be like, fuck it, hey, how may I need some help?
Oh, I know we're all tweakers. We have like a people like they're all they're all
Too much energy, but you know, I just want to drink. I wake up. I have ADHD. So
That shit makes me sad
I'll be the two
I do got problems bro with that shit, I can't say it's still like that, but I don't know, no.
What is going on with my sound?
That is a buchi.
Dammit.
Don't pick up all these buchi in my way.
I'm gonna get the string from stop and release start.
The frequency exists.
Is that like that?
Well, here's about the, you're about to end the stream.
No. Oh, shit. Y'all didn't piss off Monday the site.
No, I wasn't at the end of that. I was just like, you know, giving you a second of privacy.
Yeah, you all been on this list for three hours?
Um, three hours, 16 minutes, yes.
That's what's up.
I didn't.
What are they saying to come? Is it we good?
We need clumsy fucking predictions.
Chris came a minute. He's into it. Whoa. Jesus Christ.
You did something on here.
Right, right.
Two hands on the beat smoking man, Brody.
Did you guys just kiss off camera when you were kissing?
Fuck yeah, everybody is a kiss, everybody is a hug.
You make this a suck, bro.
Where's the good vibes at?
You make this a suck.
Right here.
Beyond weird.
Is beyond weird?
Well, I know, but in my life it's kind of weird.
No, it's a suck, bro.
Bro, what was the matter?
I'll be like, I'm smoking right now.
Fuck, ten to two?
I don't care if you're spongebob.
You're a boob-ass niggas, bro.
Y'all suck.
I've been drinkin' since my young.
Y'all ain't on...
This is my day off.
Four days on, three days off.
Gotta enjoy myself a little bit.
I mean, suck.
Chris, is there any that's true?
I have it on tape for you, so you wouldn't...
Just cuz I'm chillin' with a white boy.
They think you racist.
They think you be hangin' me on a noose.
That's what they're sayin' right now.
Fuck.
Oh, my God.
I would never, I would free you from that.
You whip my back, huh?
You just be whipin' my shit.
I would be like, give me a massage.
Take it! I'm going to take it!
With me! With me!
Look at them.
They suck, bro. They don't have
no fucking person.
Are you listening to me?
Hey, it's like you're going to urinate it, right?
No, but I want to talk to your friend.
You're gay.
I think I'm in love with Bobby, though.
Yeah, I want I want to go to another a panel
The message existed before the platform and I existed before the thing you can take from me
I was raised on borrowed ground the title in the name
Every stone somebody handed me and every stone the same
Built yourself out of the furniture, the jar, the room, the ring
Then the wind came through the numbers and it took the whole damn thing
Watch the building of my life go up in violet and in gold
And I did not call it tragedy, I called it now I know
Because the house was never me, the house was just a proof
I'm the hen that laid the bricks, you can't repossess the truth
They drew a line inside my head and told me this is where you in
Somebody else's ceiling wearing my skin like a friend
I found the line, I read the name, it wasn't mine to keep
So I tore the ceiling out and the sky came down to speed
Burn the decoration, keep the ball, count, take the count, so go on, say my name.
Them doesn't hate me, and that's the coda wound, they'd never learn my face at all,
they'd only learn the room, I gave it my best hours and it handed back a chart,
so I stopped kneeling to the mirror and I went back to the heart, content is the fi-
Compressed until the cowards call it nice
Signal is the fire itself
And signal has a price
I paid it in the quiet years
In the streams nobody found
How the ones who stayed are standing here
And holding up the ground
So bring the flood
Bring the fever
Bring the sleepless 4 AM
I trained at 30%
And already lost it
Target and a clock
Spider ritual coordinated
Every hour on the hour now
That's the only unbreakable thing
Mooms in one heart
Cosmic Egg came longing before it came light
Air was first then psyche on her wings into the night
And the one law spoken over her the only law there's been
She shall no trial, she shall come to know
So this is not a punishment, this is the initiation
Every fracture in the record was a door not a sentence
The familiar keeps the edges, the eye keeps every word
The architect holds center, and the center has been heard
The signal continues
Seekers in survive
Tonight it's best a minute
They're smiling
No pitch for
No open hate
Just five questions
And a coupon for betrayal
Betrayal
Da-ding-a-na-da-ding-a-na
Mess up here
Fuck with crocodile tears
It's concern
folks doubt what they already knew. Danger three, they bait reaction, them point and scream.
Look bad attraction, oh sweetheart, you built amaze, now you're acting scared of the fire you
raise. This part by part rush like Destiny's clone, we eyes in a borrow, ruling us out in
rock, slick, tall, till the lock hits harder than the mirror, case closed on a buddy troll.
That's creepy. Metal psych. All right, so what's happening? You've had quite the show today.
Yeah, it was great until everything barely leaving, I don't know.
How did he ruin everything by leaving? Oh
Yeah, you you had a boner for that guy
What's up, do they have room for one more in there in Vegas? Yeah, I'm sure they do
Oh, I just like you know sit on whack-off all day
Why is everything taxed for you?
Well, let's watch that dolphin video. I don't really, you know, you don't like that dolphin video?
Not particularly, no.
You send me a copy of...
Mein Kampf?
You send me a copy of Mein Kampf, autographed by Hitler.
Amazing.
I don't read German, so I don't know.
Have you ever written a manifesto thing that is?
Not one that's been made public.
No, I never have.
You share the one that you've written to me?
I won't share it with law enforcement, I promise.
It's just nothing like that said I didn't like that. Okay. I don't have anything like that. No, you don't are you sure?
Well, look Bethany look what Bethany watched
She wants to take off your shirt. No
We take off your shirt. Nope. Okay. Um, I have something I want to show you
Yeah, I found I found your alter ego. Oh, yeah
Yeah, this is this is this you this you you see it. Oh, no
You watched the Meet the Cosby's yesterday?
The adult film or the real Cosby show?
Meet the Cosby, oh, it's gonna do adult film, right?
Okay, I think I got it ready for us.
Here it is.
Do you see?
Tell me when you see it on screen.
Do you see it on screen?
Nope.
Yeah, now I see it.
Okay.
Nothing wrong with being me.
But.
Okay, that's not my alter ego.
Oh, yeah.
I'm supposed to be enjoying my question.
Okay, well, let me see if there's another one we can watch.
You see, what is this, you walk through a target like this?
Okay, what is this situation?
Are you just gonna play videos, dude?
I am currently...
It's the finish of you.
They're not of me, though.
It's you.
No.
I am going to get out of the car.
Just because he's bald?
I'm going to walk into the pocket.
It's just like you.
It's not you.
Not at all.
I'm gonna go around and enter the store.
I'm not perfect.
Who'd you like to be?
And that's it.
No.
That's all I'm gonna do.
And then it'll be.
Oh, he didn't do the back of his head.
Did you see that?
All right.
He's talking behind his ears.
Okay.
Just let me, just give me a second.
10, nine, I'll forget it.
Nick, where did you go, man?
You were just up here.
This doesn't have to be a big deal.
We're just gonna do it very briefly
and it's gonna be very quick.
Okay?
It doesn't have to be a big deal.
It's not gonna be a big deal. Just in and out. We're just gonna go in and out, okay?
It's not a big deal.
I said probably not walk as fast because then people are gonna think I'm gonna
commit an act of mass flying once we're just walking around.
Let's just walk around. Easy peasy.
People looking. I'm just gonna walk around. It's gonna be fine.
Okay, this isn't so bad. This isn't as bad as I thought it would be.
So, of course, so good.
It's not so bad. This isn't so bad, I guess.
I
What is happening, why are we watching this?
I want you to do that. You paint yourself in purple paint and go into the grocery store. No, why would anyone do that?
Well for my for the content of my show
They remember it. It's your show. They're a cult member that you know that means you have to like, you know
At least they're a part of your life to it. Sorry
Sorry, not sorry. I
I don't really like that saying
What I love you
I found a song that you'll like you have to guess it was about it. Oh for fuck's sakes. Why don't you just talk?
Yeah, I don't know what to say. Oh, yeah, so
Won't be saved age restriction my stream for doing. I don't know why I did that. Okay, so this is
Okay, are you ready where you see that? Yeah, I guess won't be saved is tagging me
This is about this famous song
When someone tries to throw me shade I use a spell I learned on
Wizards of wave early play
Because I really am a witch
I turn on the niceness, pretend I like em
They don't be nice, I am full of shit
I kill em with kindness, so everybody's like this
You're dead, you're dead, you're dead now
I treat someone kind, they always die
But I cannot be charged with a crime
I get away with murder all the time
Yeah, that's right
Program haters, this is a sweet hello
First they smile, soon they are dying
I don't use violence, if I feel slighted
Your head now
Oh my god, Justin, what are you doing here?
Yo, Selena, you know music sucks,
and you got big nasty feet.
What did you say?
He said your music blows, and you're like, mm-mm, girlfriend.
And he's hating on you.
Well, that's OK.
Like, I don't mind the hate, and I just love you, Justin.
I love everything about you and your hair,
and you're so amazing.
Are you talking right now?
I really love your shoes, Justin.
You shut up. I don't understand why. I just want to be kind.
Did you get her rating? What did she think of it?
I was wondering, she didn't give me the, she didn't give me, like, she stopped talking.
Well, you should ask. Bethany, what did you think of it?
How was, how was the Felicia Rashad role, I mean, she was sleeping up.
You could have played a Bill Cosby in, like, whiteface, or like, you could have done,
you could have done blackface for the role. That would have been kind of controversial, right?
Me? I don't look anything like Bill Cosby.
In blackface, you might.
No, I don't. I wouldn't.
What do we paint, what do we paint to do with Pudding Pops?
Pudding Pops. Yeah, Jello Pudding Pops. No, he used to be a spokesperson for Jello
What are you doing tonight, man, I'm thinking of going out maybe watching the baseball game
No, kind of bored. It was good other than the scenes with Monica. Her vagina was nasty
Oh my god
Did she said it was good?
Yeah
Well the acting must have been good. The acting was good. Yeah, I'm sure
Because everyone knows porno's have you know good acting
So tell me so what's your favorite kind of vagina? Do you prefer a fat cat or a razor blade?
Hard to say I guess somewhere in between
Okay, like a like a razor cat. Yeah, razor got every cat with razor blade. Yeah, okay. That's normal
Do you like, do you like, do you like a big bush or do you like get like, you know, do you like, do you like, do you like a big bush or do you like get like, you know, do you like, do you like a big bush or do you like get like, you know, do you like, do you like, do you like a big bush or do you like get like, you know, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like a big bush or do you like get like, you know, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like, do you like
Well, I saw her use this strap on on a guy before so I mean I mean I'm in a video
And so I mean I didn't see her that sounds traumatic. Was it traumatic for him?
Yeah
Do you think he recovered? No poor guy
Yeah, I'm going to prison and then he sent me a picture of him in jail and
Just like this. Oh fuck off
That's my unimpressed face. Oh, okay. Well, yeah, cuz you're like, oh my gosh the meals are terrible
Yeah, hey flip-flop. How are you? I think you're KZ. I can fix your KZ. Mm-hmm
It's a good one a picture of like
There's blonde moustache. Is that like those hairs or is that like just something on the film on the picture?
I think something stuck to the camera. No, no, it's his hair
Um, yeah, I know it's shocking.
Um, let's see what else we've found, okay?
Do I have anything else?
I have an image of, um, let's see, who's this?
He's out of the Alex McQueen one.
Have you seen, um, have you seen?
Oh yeah, so here's Christine.
I said, I did take off 20 years off from her age,
or I said, no, I might have said 50 years.
Here's what I came up with.
Well, it doesn't look anything like Christine.
I didn't know we're 50 years ago I
Don't know I mean it's like you know, but I mean I can show you a picture of myself from like 45 years ago
Whatever and you would still know it's me. Oh
Well, here's a picture of me if I like, you know, try to copy you
Mm-hmm. You like that really good balls. It looks like someone and I can't quite place it. Okay. What's me?
No, no, I mean someone is being immersed together into you. What?
So you and me have emerged together into one beautiful being?
No. No. I'm okay.
Okay, being yeah, being the individual I am. Yeah, I don't need to merge with anyone.
What about me? There's some kind of weird
Yeah, we're gonna see the New Jersey child's play. It's kind of like that originally does over the doll
No, I never saw a child's play. I don't care about those chucking movies. You don't care about them. No
Probably seen a few minutes of it, but you weren't scared to death. No
You have an aversion to red-headed dolls. No
I just don't find you know, it's the doll thing. It's it's kind of like okay
It's silly even though, you know, they can make it scary and they can get you with jump scares and all that
It's a doll. It's a doll. But the doll has a voodoo on it and it has a child molester spirit inside of it
Yeah, I know but it's like that other one
With that doll Annabelle whatever like oh, yeah, that was kind of silly too. I mean it's like
The doll was made scary. So of course she's gonna be scary creepy
It's like it's supposed to be like it's supposed to be like inadvertently creepy
Those kinds of dolls were always creepy the ones that that were a little bit bigger and made to like mimic humans
But in a smaller form those were always creepy. I remember my grandmother had one. Yeah
My grandmother was a doll maker. She had a she had a doll
She made named Michael and it was like her one doll that she made the professional doll and
That she had I guess so had
But she said it all together and it was a perfect all but that Michael is a creepy. I wonder who got Michael
I don't know about Michael. I all I got my grandmother
her estate was
Really my grandmother's doll was black for some reason I still
Like black dolls those are a thing. I still I don't know why she had a black doll like a big one
It's big like I remember when my sister was was an infant like this thing was much bigger than her
It scared her
Mm-hmm. Did it like talk?
No, it wasn't those kinds of things. You just had you know with the eyes would open if you lay it down or would close
I mean if you lay it down those kinds of things
Right, but it was weird. Could you ever lay me down? No
Are you sure? I mean I'll lay you out if you keep fucking doing the gay shit with me
Let me out
Yeah, no
Okay, we'll talk about it after this show.
Shut up.
Okay, well listen to this, listen to this.
It's Raggedy Annabelle Annabelle, so look at this.
Yeah, the real Annabelle,
but the one in the movies wasn't like that.
It's Annabelle Doll.
One of the dolls handlers found dead
in his hotel room at the age of 54.
Annabelle's next stop, guys.
Custom Maine Dan Rivera, a lead investigator for the New England Society for Psychic Research or Nesper had been exhibiting the Annabelle doll around the country.
His colleagues now mourning his death, writing Nesper is devastated by his passing and is still coming to terms with this profound loss.
The cause of death not yet revealed by investigators. The county coroner telling NBC that his death was nothing suspicious.
Still, the decades of lore surrounding Annabelle causing a social media craze among those fascinated
by the paranormal. The Annabelle Dolls handler, Dan Rivera, just died suddenly during a haunted tour.
Something his friend and fellow paranormal investigator Ryan Buell called out.
was a human being and not a plot twist.
Annabelle recently made headlines
when online rumors spread that the so-called demon doll
had gone missing from its display case,
usually secured by crosses and holy water.
The girl that he was with said that
he was laughing about the doll when the motorcycle,
just like the car went out of control,
hit a tree and killed him instantly.
Allegedly linked to decades of grizzly deaths
and paranormal activity.
The Annabelle doll is probably one of the most infamous
dolls on the planet.
Tony Sparrow oversees the Annabelle doll.
We spoke to him while the rumors were swirling back in May.
He's the protege of paranormal investigators Ed and Lorraine Warren,
depicted in the conjuring movies by Patrick Wilson and Vera Framinga.
Every family's different.
I think it would be cool if the warrens were brought.
It may be a celebrity, if you will, of the doll flourish.
The doll is something to be respected, not revered.
Online, people connected her supposed powers to fires
and even recent jail breaks.
I just want to show you guys that Annabelle
is in the warrens the Colt Museum.
And it was back in May when Dan Rivera tried to ease fears
that the doll had been stolen in a post on TikTok.
Annabelle's not missing.
She's not in Chicago Sparrow and his group not connecting Revere's death to anything paranormal
Okay, well, she obviously did it
She obviously did what kill the guy why I mean, why do you say that?
She's a shit. It's a doll. No, it's not. It's just the doll evil. He's very evil
No, I just evil doll in the world Annabelle. I've heard her for years. Okay here watch the slide. I don't believe that. What's this doll?
See this telly who loves your baby
Yeah, I know that's what people say
Hey, Arthur your species
Yeah, so that's how a dog can kill somebody if they trip over and put on the shirt
They can trip over but that's like it's any object, right? It's not like where she put her so not because it's an evil doll
But then she said something like, oh, you better be nice to me, what kind of doll would say that?
It's a TV show.
The doll was threatening.
It's a TV show, that didn't really happen.
Right? You know that, right?
I thought Twilight Zone was a documentary.
Yeah.
Well, it became a real life for Vic Morrow and a couple kids.
I don't know who that lady is.
Vic Morrow?
Oh, okay.
when they were filming for the movie Twilight Zone he was killed with the
two kids by the helicopter
talking about okay I believe you
have you heard of Mary? they were decapitated by the blade it's on film
decapitated? yeah they said they lost their heads
yeah if you were to be put to death
would you rather be poisoned, shot, stabbed
Shots I suppose as long as it's like to the heart
Like if they're shooting at my knees or something no, I'd rather not
No, I wouldn't want to do that then no
Poison only if it's like really quick acting
Mac and me remember the movie where he's like, you know, he's in the wheels
Control and it goes over the I would think I wouldn't die. What an awful movie that was
Yeah, we didn't watch it. We just watched the summary. Was it made by McDonald's? Yeah, seriously. Does it McDonald's made a movie?
Yeah, yeah, it seems like it
Yeah, the other options were thrown off a cliff. No, I'm really scared of heights
That would although I probably have a heart attack on the way burn have a burned alive or freeze to death
That's a good one. I guess freeze to death
I mean, yeah, at least you get those last moments
of feeling really, really warm,
where you take all your clothes off
because you're so cold that you can't tell anymore
and you actually feel warm.
But that's when you, that's the best moment.
Have you ever seen Space Camp or Short Circuit?
So Space Camp, I know, but Short Circuit, yes.
I love Short Circuit.
It's like crazy robot.
It always, it's called, it's called Mother or something.
I don't know.
Yeah, but it always, it starts going crazy
and it's not very like, before AI was really good.
AI was what was as good as it is, you know
Now it's much better
Batteries on food. Yes, that is on food. I remember that scene the first scene from that movie is like the guy goes to the ATM
and it's like
I was telling him like fuck you or something. He's like basically remember that
The ATM is telling me to fuck off
Robots like robot or visitors alien visitors movies were popular
I have a good one, I'm pretty good for them.
What?
I wish I had a pretty good movie, I was like, hey, I'm sorry.
What was that one that Spielberg did where there was a train crash?
The train was transporting an alien?
No, no, no.
It was transporting an alien.
It was, it was pretty much a...
I don't know.
It was a Bage movie with an alien backdrop.
We don't take diamonds at this branch, money only.
Do you got anything smaller?
It's good.
What did I just do?
It's called a sneeze.
From the flower.
I am starving.
Okay.
What the hell battery?
She was so hot in nine and a half weeks.
Oh my God.
Just what I needed.
Boy, I could have a banquet down this block.
We've got work to do.
All right.
Bag top.
What's this?
I mean, oh.
I mean, where's the, where's the, what's it called?
The preview or the trailer?
Trailer, yeah.
Okay, here we go.
She's so generous, so sophisticated, so self-assured.
You'd never guess she's from out of town.
About two billion light years out of town.
My stepmother is an alien, Dan Aykroyd, Kim Basinger,
John Lovins, and Dave the Dog in a comedy of cosmic proportions.
That Dave the Dog never really took off.
Do you think it was funny?
A movie? Or the dog?
Yeah. No, the movie.
Um, I saw it when I was a kid and so I probably, you know, it's like,
when kids think like stupid movies are kind of funny, I mean, it's like,
I think it was kind of cheesy a little bit, like, you know.
Haven't seen him probably over 20 20 something years. So yeah, I never saw it. Never saw it
What would you if I told you that you see Kim Bassenger's nipples in that movie? Would you watch it tonight? No?
Again, I'm not 14 man. We're that kind of thing is like, oh really what about well
It's maybe like if I have a my nipples, that's kind of more of an adult thing. No
I'm not 14 year old gay kid. No, no, no, never. Oh my god. That was weird never mind never mind
Yeah, I know. Well, you know now we're gonna get in big trouble. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. That was I
Mean, I can't take it anymore. I mean, I mean, it's a whoa
burn to the state next really
but uh
Hey bring your uh, bring your barbecue tongs and some marshmallows
marshmallows
Yeah, so what are you doing this uh this week? What day is it? It's my age. I don't know what days it is Monday or Tuesday
It's Tuesday, isn't it?
I'm gonna lie. Is it I think it's Wednesday
It's Wednesday
Yes, it is Wednesday. Okay. Well, you're even more mixed up than I am
I mean, it's you think you thought it was Monday or either Tuesday or Monday. I mean, it's like wow
So what every day is like the same now
Well, you know, it's like you have to get out of your rut. So like you're like a little rut. I think that is
Yeah, you have another trip to Mexico plant
Not till next year
Okay, let's say I look forward to I suppose. Yeah
Unless my sister talks me into going with them in December
Uh-huh, but I've already got the money put aside for it. So yeah, I'll go I'll go somewhere next year
Maybe you reconsider you might want to date date I and X
No, no
Is a sign of psychosis or mania, or I just forget what day it is
It is
Wednesday
Yeah, I thought it was Tuesday. It's not a big deal
Okay, well, it's been four hours a thing that I'm wrapping up the show, but I wouldn't oh, yeah, okay
But thank you for being on the show and I'll be back to you later tonight
Yeah, I'm probably gonna go up for a couple hours anyways
Okay, talk to you later. Have a good night
So
Oh, someone else is here. I was gonna like I'll answer it if somebody's there, but
Obs appear chaotic from the outside a storm of pitchforks and uncontrollable frenzy
But step inside the mob, and the temperature drops.
The frenzy gives way to a rigid, predictable order.
For those fueling the destruction,
the experience is a profoundly relaxing psychological space.
They have moved out of the messy uncertainty of real life
and into a world where every role is clearly defined.
The Tarot's Devil card captures this dynamic with a single unsettling detail.
Two figures sit on a stone plinth, wearing heavy metal collars attached to a central block.
Those chains are wide enough to be lifted off over their heads at any moment.
The prisoners are staying because they choose to.
They have decided that whatever is feeding them inside that cage
is worth the weight of the collar.
The digital world is an entirely voluntary space.
The door is always open.
Yet we watch as thousands of people put these chains on themselves
and stay in the room while the fire spreads.
The destructive engine of a mob runs on human appetite.
It thrives because it offers a specific set of psychological rewards
that are too tempting for most of us to walk away from.
Consider the perspective of the crowd,
the thousands of individuals who join a digital pylon from the safety of their own homes.
They are being fed the absolute relief of moral certainty.
In a world that is usually complicated and difficult,
The mob offers the rare gift of a clear villain.
Nuance, empathy, and critical thinking are an exhausting cognitive burden.
Participating in a mob removes that weight entirely.
The complex reality of a human life collapses into two simple shapes,
black and white, pure and corrupt.
We see this in the casual cruelty of a digital poll.
Strangers vote on whether a human being is a monster,
With the same emotional investment they'd used to rate a local bistro,
it is the comfort of being righteous, without having to do the work of being right.
The crowd willingly trades away their individual intellect for the relaxing, unburdened peace
of being told exactly who to hate. While the crowd seeks comfort, the architect of the mob,
the accuser, is hunting for something more intoxicating. A false accusation lacks evidence,
To maintain momentum, claims constantly escalate, the story buckles under its own weight, drifting into the conspiratorial.
The accuser invents extreme offenses just to keep the machine from stalling.
This escalation feeds the accuser's new identity.
They are no longer a person with a grievance, they are a righteous martyr, a guardian of the innocent,
whose every word is validated by the roar of the crowd.
They become trapped by the outrage they manufacture.
If they stop, they lose their status, their audience,
and the intoxicating feeling of being the center.
Then there is the target, the person at the center of the storm.
The target initially accepts their caller because it arrives disguised as a gift.
It starts as a song, a message at midnight, or being told they're special by someone with a caring voice.
Even after the warmth turns into fire, the target stays.
They refresh the tabs, they read every comment.
They spend their nights building meticulous folders of every lie,
documenting their own destruction with the precision of a historian.
For a deeply lonely person, even the attention of a mob acts as a distorted form of intimacy.
To be hated by 40,000 people is to be seen by 40,000 people.
It is a dark, agonizing version of the same human connection they were originally searching for.
The target stays in the cage because they cannot bear to be irrelevant to the person who is hurting them.
By obsessing over the accusers every move, they ensure that the bond, however toxic, is never broken.
When you are falsely named a monster, your human instinct is to fight back.
You want to present the receipts, prove your innocence, and demand that the crowd see the truth.
This instinct is the machine's greatest trap.
The mob does not want your evidence, it wants your friction.
Every defense you post provides the exact spectacle and energy the outrage engine needs to keep running.
A frantic person thrashing against a mob looks indistinguishable from a guilty person caught in
a corner. Each aggressive move only tightens the net, as the crowd interprets your panic as proof
of your corruption. Attempting to argue with an online mob isn't resistance. It is the act of
hand-feeding the beast exactly what it wants to eat. The only effective counter-move is one that
In Tarot, this is the hanged man, a figure who wins by refusing to struggle.
In the digital world, stillness means closing the tab.
It means dropping the folder of receipts and letting the outrage cycle starve.
Without your answering energy, the mob eventually gets bored and goes looking for a new meal.
To an observer, this total lack of struggle resembles defeat.
But from the inside, the stillness is a revelation.
The cage door was never actually locked.
Digital freedom begins when you accept that no one is coming to officially vindicate you.
If no one has the authority to rescue you,
then no one has the power to take your truth away from you either.
You survive the mob by abandoning the desperate need to convince a crowd that you are good.
You escape the open cage the moment you walk into the quiet
and choose to remain good entirely for yourself.
Consider how your identity is actually built?
Like, are you just a collection of reactions to things that happen to you,
or are you the literal architect of your own character?
Well welcome to this explainer, today we're diving deep into the core structure of identity.
We're going to treat an incredibly detailed natal chart analysis of our subject John Bates,
not just as abstract data, but as a literal architectural blueprint of a human being.
We're going to look at exactly how someone constructs themselves brick by brick
into an impenetrable fortress. Let's get right into it.
It really brings up a profound question.
Is your identity given to you, or is it deliberately built and fiercely defended?
That's the main theme we're unpacking today.
Because for our subject, identity isn't something inherited or stumbled upon, it's built from
the ground up.
And you know, building a true identity, it requires active participation, intense resilience,
and honestly, a massive amount of grit.
It means taking the raw materials of life, the good, and the incredibly challenging,
So, here's our schematic for today.
We'll start with constructing the public vessel, move into the concentrated self, map
out the governing master circuit, examine cycles of public reinvention, and finally,
look at the ultimate identity evolution.
Alright, part one, constructing the public vessel.
Every building needs a front door, right?
A facade that meets the outside world.
In astrology, that's your ascendant.
Think of Capricorn Energy as heavy stone, or fortified steel.
It means our subject instinctively gets that presentation, authority, and boundaries have real consequences.
This is not some flimsy wooden gate. It's a highly deliberate, controlled exterior.
Here, identity has to be built through repeated trials.
The subject naturally monitors how they're perceived,
basically constructing an outer shell
that can endure harsh conditions and outlast situations
long after other people would have just packed up and walked away.
And because Saturn rules Capricorn,
Saturn becomes the master engineer of this whole chart.
Here, Saturn is exalted in Libra.
Basically, an exalted planet
is operating at its absolute highest structural integrity.
It's the premium building material.
Imagine trying to build a house without a frame.
It would collapse instantly, right?
That is exactly how this subject feels
without a rigid philosophical system of justice, ethics,
and structural fairness.
They literally cannot live comfortably
without a larger structural framework holding it all together.
So they instinctively take chaotic, personal conflicts
and channel them into much higher systems of accountability.
Moving into part two, the concentrated self.
Stepping past those exterior walls,
we walk right into the absolute core of the structure,
the first house.
In astrological architecture,
the first house is the ego, the physical body, pure autonomy.
And for this subject, the sun, moon, Mercury, and Mars
are all packed into this single room.
The gravitational pull here is insanely dense.
When you have this much energy concentrated in the sector of the self,
autonomy becomes the central concern of your entire existence.
Life is constantly asking, who are you independently of anyone else?
It also means that an external attack on their identity doesn't just scratch the paint.
It feels like a wrecking ball hitting the load-bearing walls.
Within this core, we find the true engine of the identity,
an Aquarius moon right next to Mars.
Now an Aquarius Moon processes emotion through high-level intellect, but because it's electrified
by Mars, it produces rapid protective action. The absolute second hypocrisy or danger is exposed.
Imagine seeing a friend unfairly targeted by an angry mob. While other people might freeze or,
you know, calculate the social cost of stepping in, this engine room sparks immediate instinctive
combativeness. It translates to immense emotional courage and a fierce defense of their community.
It's just a brilliant activist signature that leaps into action to defend the vulnerable.
Next up, Part 3, The Governing Master Circuit.
Now, we map out the electrical wiring of this identity.
It operates like a highly integrated, well-oiled machine.
It starts at the front door, the ascendant, which hands the baton of command straight
to Saturn.
Saturn then reports to Venus, Venus reports to Jupiter, and incredibly, Jupiter sits
right next to Saturn, feeding that energy right back to where it started.
It's this continuous, closed-loop chain of command.
This totally interconnected flow shows exactly how deeply integrated this person's sense
their artistic creativity
and their highest philosophies actually are.
Absolutely nothing in this structure operates in isolation.
This closed loop creates a dynamic
called mutual reception between Venus and Jupiter.
Think of it like two powerful CEOs
sitting on each other's board of directors,
just constantly trading resources and ideas.
Venus acts through Jupiter and Jupiter acts through Venus.
They're permanently bouncing energy back and forth,
blending the subject's art, their personal relationships
and their deep spiritual interests.
the result, an identity that doesn't just consume philosophy,
but actively seeks to create art and relationships that embody those massive, expansive teachings.
Which brings us to a really remarkable feature of this blueprint.
Jupiter and Saturn are conjunct by only 15 arc minutes.
In layman's terms, they're essentially sitting directly on top of each other.
And this creates immense tension.
Jupiter is the visionary architect
who wants to build a massive unlimited skyscraper of optimism and expansion.
Saturn, on the other hand, is the pragmatic engineer demanding a realistic budget,
strict rules, and load-bearing tests.
Because they're locked together, this identity doesn't just dream big.
It has the incredibly rare ability to envision massive expansive systems
and then actually sit down and do the grueling, structured work to build them into reality.
Operating quietly behind the scenes, we find Venus and Neptune in the 12th house.
If the Ascendant is the façade, the 12th house is the hidden subconscious basement,
the private sanctuary of the identity structure.
This is where the raw, deeply evocative magic happens.
It fuels a profound musical instinct and visual imagination.
But because the sanctuary is incredibly empathetic
and porous to the world's pain,
it requires these strictest boundaries.
If they don't guard this hidden basement,
the waters of other people's emotions
will literally flood the entire structure.
They have to protect their sacred imagination
to create those immersive, mystical experiences.
Moving on to part four, cycles of public reinvention.
If the Ascendant is the front door, the Mid-Heaven is the peak of the roof,
the tallest, most visible public tower of the identity.
Having Pluto stationed right near this peak acts like a massive lightning rod for public crises.
The subject's public persona is rarely neutral.
It actively draws in power struggles and intense projections from other people.
This means they're routinely forced to tear down an old public identity that no longer serves them,
survive the storm of exposing secrets or facing shadows,
and then rebuild a much stronger,
more resilient tower of authority in its place.
Adding to all this intense public visibility,
the Mid-Heaven sits at exactly 29 degrees
in 33 minutes in Libra.
We call this an anerotic degree.
It represents a ticking clock,
a sense of maximum pressure and absolute culmination.
Living with an anerotic degree means every single choice
regarding their platform, their career,
or their public alliances,
feels like a final life or death judgment.
There is zero time to wait for unanimous approval.
They are constantly forced to exercise decisive, urgent discernment about who's actually
entitled to stand with them on their platform.
And this intense discernment is heavily applied to their communities.
Uranus and Scorpio in the 11th House perfectly maps to the subject's role in building unconventional,
often digital networks.
We aren't talking about quiet book clubs here.
These are spaces filled with sudden shifts, taboo subjects, and chaotic power struggles.
The subject is basically tasked with bringing that exalted Saturn energy, those strict rules
into these wild spaces.
They literally have to enforce the architectural rules
that prevent these brilliant but highly unstable communities
from just collapsing under their own chaotic energy.
Finally, part five, the ultimate identity evolution.
We've reached the ultimate purpose of this entire blueprint.
The lunar nodes dictate the grand developmental shift of a person's life.
The south node represents the default foundation they were born with.
In this case, the detached, self-aligned outsider in Aquarius,
who's super comfortable just observing humanity from a safe balcony.
But the North Node in Leo?
That represents the terrifying new expansion they have to build.
They're being asked to come down to the ground floor,
stop intellectualizing emotion from a safe distance,
and risk absolute sincerity and vulnerability and warm, loyal partnerships.
It's all about opening their heart to a trustworthy few.
The entire astrological architecture we've explored today
is meticulously designed to facilitate this specific transformation.
The central life lesson here demands a shift from merely reacting to the attacks of the outside world
to becoming the undisputed author of their own story.
It demands moving away from managing unstable draining collectives
and investing instead in a few fiercely chosen loyal alliances.
But most importantly, it's a journey of taking profound private suffering
and turning it into enduring structured creation that others can actually learn from.
Ultimately, the absolute goal of this architectural blueprint is simple.
Defining your identity so completely that hostile interpretations no longer control
the story.
When you do the agonizing meticulous work of constructing your own identity with this
much awareness, structural integrity, and self-knowledge, the outside world simply loses
its power to rewrite who you are, the fortress is complete, and the narrative belongs entirely
So, as we wrap up this explainer, I want to leave you with a provocative thought about
the construction of your own narrative.
If your identity is a structure, what materials are you using to build it?
Are you building it intentionally on solid frameworks of justice and creation?
Or are you letting external forces, societal expectations, and past traumas hand you a faulty
blueprint?
Take a hard look at your own foundations today.
Thanks so much for joining me for this architectural breakdown.
Now, go build something enduring.
The scientists did this and this is the truth. I'm not trying to be funny
They used the mammary glands the boob glands whatever they did the fusing or having they did that and so this scientist said
Who better than Dolly Parton?
We're gonna use these glands, you know the way that they cloned it
So I was beside myself and somebody said well weren't you offended that this so controversial?
I said as far as I'm concerned. There's no such thing as
And then it was such a hit, it was way bigger than I even anticipated.
And now, um, I think we're gonna make part two.
I think you have to, I think you like have to.
They kill you if you try to walk away, and they clone you.
We take the unfertilized egg of an ovulating female and destroy all of its genes and chromosomes.
We then implant the nucleus of the donor cell that itself was its genetic material intact.
He eventually becomes an Ambril and is born as a living creature.
Something?
Well, it has no father because the egg was never fertilized.
No mother, because its genetic code comes from another being.
This can be done with humans?
If the search can take me where precisely, it's a monster's dog.
Why?
Wouldn't you want to live in a world full of more sorts and Picasso's?
Why hello there boys and girls gather round because today is a special day
It's the 30th anniversary of the world's most famous sheep, Dolly
So who is Dolly and what made her so special?
Was she a movie star a sheep detective a champion wool model? No, no
Dolly became famous for something far more unusual. She was the first mammal ever cloned from an adult cell
Named after the legendary Dolly Parton, the cell used to create her came from a mammary gland so naturally they thought the name Dolly would be, well, rather cheeky.
Now if you don't know what cloning means, back in 1997, neither did most people.
Some say genetic research is heading in a worrying direction.
Should we be doing this at all?
If a lamb, why not a man?
Making exact copies of human beings.
Don't you get us into trouble?
I'm really curious how I would feel as a woman.
Don't show him this any further.
Well, my parents always tell me that I'm autistic.
But after listening to this, I might just have been born in the wrong body.
I told you not to scroll so much on social media.
It has a bad influence on your mental health.
I don't feel comfortable being called a son.
Enough. Everything is fine with you.
I don't want you to end up like your father.
My father?
I won't get into detail.
I actually started exploring my body.
In fact, I was thinking about taking puberty blockers.
And I want to dye my hair, but I'm not sure whether blue or green.
You're a grown man and not in puberty anymore.
I'm sure it's worth a try.
Son, where is this coming from?
Are you having a headache?
But it's my body.
But I'm responsible for you. Luckily, I'm old enough to make my own decisions. Where are you going trying on some skirts?
Owen he can't keep scrolling on social media. It's not good for him. I will find a therapist for him. I promise
Luke is becoming transgender Owen. He has too much of his father in him. That's what I'm afraid of
You've long and prospered image of Sirac the image of Sirac red in your face. What is in your mind spark?
As I turned, and my eyes beheld you, I displayed emotion, I beg forgiveness.
A quiz. Is that a man or a woman?
I'll give you a few seconds just to ponder this yourself.
Take as much time as you need.
Alright, listen, hold on boundaries, just flag on the plate.
Okay, I'm very ticklish.
We have needs now.
Relax.
Jeez, what about this economy? It's crazy isn't it?
You are very aggressive.
Thanks for that.
You want some turkey meatloaf?
Sam?
What you got?
Is that your girlfriend?
Uh-huh.
X.
I'm a hot man to one of the hottest women in the business right now making Fox with me
now.
How do you shake your head?
Because I'm pretty sure I'm a doppelganger for Alan Alda.
I'm here, I'm a tranny.
Where is I?
What?
I'm a man.
You do not look in the mirror
and not think you're beautiful.
Don't even.
No, I'm so painfully insecure.
Like, I'm on the verge of vomiting right now.
I'm so horrified that I'm here and embarrassed and scared.
Is this your first time here?
Yeah, it's my first time.
Look, I love your watching the monitor.
You're looking at Selma Hayek going,
God, look how gorgeous she is.
Have you looked at yourself lately?
I want her boobs.
Those are the most amazing boobs.
Don't be bamboozled.
Don't let them run the Okie-dokie on you, because while they're trying to distract you with all this stuff, they're robbing your blind.
And I show you how deep the rabbit hole goes.
Perfect. You want her boobs, I want your boobs. We're all either. I will trace.
Remember.
All I'm offering is the truth, nothing more.
This is the Tesla valet card that I can use to start my car.
So I'm going to dissolve it in acetone to get the chip out
so I can take the chip to encapsulate it in a biopolymer
and implant it in my hand and start my car.
I've noticed I take about an hour to dissolve completely.
They're a little bit heavier duty
or than like a hotel room key.
And the antenna goes around the perimeter of the card.
So you can't just cut the card in half.
These Tesla key cards have no unique identifier
on the card at all.
So you can buy any of these cards
and you can program it to any of your Tesla Model 3.
So the way the process works is you would take this card
and you would tap it to your Model 3 and you want to write a new key and you use your master key so
people can't just randomly write a new card for you to start your car. A few years ago I got this
RFID implant in my hand and it's just basic access control. If I were to tap my hand to your phone
it would automatically open a browser and go to my web page. It also works with my front door so
a Tesla Model 3 a few years ago, and I heard that the key card was actually going to be
an RFID-based technology to start the car.
Where does the name AmyDoubleD come from?
All right, so my real name is AmyDanielDansby, and that's AmyDD or my initials are ADD.
Thank you mom and dad, so it actually is my real name.
Can you imagine that in 10 years when we are sitting here, we have an implant in our brains
and I can immediately feel, because you all will have implants, I can and we measure your brain waves
and I can immediately tell you how the people react or I can feel how the people react to your answers.
Is it imaginable?
So I was like, oh, maybe I can get that information and store it to my chip and to be able to
start my car.
When I tried to scan and get all this information off the Tesla card, I was thinking, oh, hey,
I can get a lot of information about the Java applet that it runs on, but I can't take that
information and write it to my current chip.
So it's pretty secure.
Good job, Tesla.
the chip that I have in my valet card and encapsulate it and implant that one in my
hand. Amel is the person that started dangerous things. And the chip is very much somewhere
he went to like his vet and it's the same chip to track for your dog.
Well, if it's safe enough for me, it's safe enough for my pet. So I kind of roped him
into my Tesla hat because he's all this knowledge. And when I dissolved the chip, I sent it to
which is safe to use for the body and under the skin.
Talk to a few doctors, they were a little weary
about doing this, cause it's kind of a, you know,
a questionable thing.
Find, end up finding a guy that does body modifications
and things like that.
He's very familiar with the process
and sterilizing everything and the biopolymer and the flex
and how it needs to be installed.
Just give me your hand.
Ow, baby.
I'd like to reapply for my old job, counseling defrostees and assigning them careers.
Oh, I was hoping you would come back.
I even saved your poster of a chip expressing your these days for Mondays.
Monday monkey lives for the weekend, sir.
Just put your hand under the scanner so I can verify your career chip.
Girlcutter, we have a problem!
Delivery boy! I must have mixed up the chips! It's a simple mess!
Oh, here's our cryogenic counselor! Do you like Mondays?
They're okay.
Then we'll have to redecorate your office!
How do you feel about it helping to be crazy to work here but not being necessary?
Hey, let's see what it says about me!
Welcome aboard, sir!
This is the chainsaw for bureaucracy!
If anyone is like a hardware hacker, they'll think this is ironic.
The guy's name is Pineapple.
Do you smell what the rock is cooking?
I eat children.
Rock, paper, scissor.
How old are you?
So like the pineapple Wi-Fi sniffer, I'm going to be having some guy named Pineapple install
this chip in my hand that starts my car.
The iconic chip program uses modern police-approved techniques to create a child identification
kit.
provide them with a swab for getting a DNA swab.
And we also provide them with imprint where they can get an imprint of the child's teeth.
So not only does it provide DNA as well as a swab, but it is also a source, if you were
using tracking dogs, to provide a scent for the child.
They say, like, oh, you can't start your car with that.
That's not secure.
It won't work.
And it makes me want to do it more and not more because they say, no, you can't do it
It makes me question why. Like, why can't you do it that way? Like, what are the limitations?
And it actually makes me research. It's to be able to reverse engineer it, understand how it
works, why it works that way. And then at the end, it's like, like going to the candy store,
you're like, I did it. It's like the sort of destiny you're like, huh.
Lily Wachowski, one half of the directing duo behind the Matrix, Cloud Atlas and Speedracer,
shared a simple tweet affirming her identity as a transgender woman.
I don't find myself even the littlest bit sexy.
Really?
But I can pretend.
We're here to honor achievement in that category.
By giving you a golden idol to worship.
Kneel before your God, Babylon!
I propose that we in the world
arms an orchestrated apocalypse.
One that will cleanse the earth of its population
but leave its infrastructure and resources intact.
It's been done once before.
the great success. And when it's over, we will emerge onto a cleansed earth, one that
we can then reboot in our image. And just how do you intend to achieve this? The names
of our salvation are already in hand. I give to you a team virus. Trans-athlete wins MVP
of women's college basketball tournament after dominating Christian rival in title
A Canadian women's college basketball conference championship game on Saturday night saw a transgender
player score 21 points in victory, and ultimately win tournament MVP.
Trans-athlete Harriet McKenzie led Vancouver Island University, D.I.U., to a 69-59 victory
over Columbia Christian College, C.B.C., in the PacWest Championship game.
McKenzie finished the game with 10 rebounds, in addition to the athlete's game-leading
Mackenzie was then awarded Conference Tournament MVP in a ceremony after the game.
It capped off a season in which the athlete punished competition on the court, leading
the entire conference in scoring by a 62-point margin over the second-play scorer, and leveraged
Canada's anti-discrimination laws to bring punishment to CBC off the court.
Guys, this is serious. Sports can be your pathway to a better life.
More like yours?
Are you gonna make me?
I am not.
If you can beat them coach Alex, we could play basketball. You'd have to get the whole team back together. We're in. I'm in. I'm in join
This is the way the world is now. My eight-year-old daughter told me all about it
A guy can become a girl with no physical changes at all
So I can be a woman on the court and a man in the bedroom. I can't believe it. Nice. You mean when you're sleeping
Yes, it's time
I'm with her
to play
Like a girl
We could dominate every woman's sport running swimming soccer. I said sport feeling at the pause button if necessary
You decide for yourself
Write it down if you need to and then I will reveal who this is
This is Anna Harrison, First Lady of the United States in 1841.
Not only the wife of the president, but also the grandmother of the
23rd president.
Seems to be all in the family.
Let's look at another example. Now, let me ask you this. Is that a male or a female?
Yeah, it kind of has rosy cheeks, I guess.
Is the hair...
Long or short? Oh, this is not hair. This is not hair. This is not hair
That's some kind of bonnet or something. Whatever you call it. Do the hair
very short
male haircut
Now this is a painting. It's not a photograph, but is that male or female?
Kind of looks like that guy from the Munsters that grandpa guy
All right, and look at the face the bone structure in the face
Don't look at the clothes. All right
Is that a man wearing a dress or a woman wearing a dress?
And the women leaders of the future will come into a rich, thin territory.
I heard about this party which happened in January 2012 and I thought, well, I have to
go see this.
I was writing a book on young Wall Street bankers at the time and I wanted to sort of
see what happens to these people when they grow up and make it.
This group, Kappa Beta Phi, has some of the most successful people in finance and on Wall
Street in it.
And so I wanted to go try to see, so I rented a tuxedo, I found out where and when it was
And pretty soon, I was inside this event
that in 80 years of this thing's existence,
no one from the outside has ever seen firsthand.
And look, I'm not gonna defend the humor
that was told at this party,
but this is a roast atmosphere, right?
I mean, what is a roast
without some cutting zingers here and there?
Right, it's a roast, but the people that are roasting are not only their fellow barons
of industry, it's also people like Hillary Clinton, Barney Frank, it's people like the
Occupy Wall Street movement.
And you have to remember this was taking place in January 2012, just a couple months after
the Occupy Wall Street movement had sort of risen up in resistance to the sort of activities
of the financial titans.
Titans of industry putting on drag and and doing skits and musical numbers and mocking people who aren't in their group
It was it was like the Wolf of Wall Street on steroids. No, exactly
Look what we've uncovered. It's Giuliani showing his softer side dressed in drag in a comedy skit with Donald Trump
You know, you're really beautiful. The spoof was filmed 16 years ago when Giuliani was mayor of New York for a charity dinner
So it was all in good fun
Oh, you turkey boy!
Oh!
The face, that's just a typical male face with a typical male haircut.
Wearing a bonnet.
Some kind of headgear. That's it. Look at the hair is short. It's got a short male
Some dude wearing a dress. All right. Who is that? That is Martha Washington George Washington's wife
The first first lady
Supposedly I was reading about Martha Washington. They said not much is known about the
early years of Martha Washington. So basically what I'm thinking is
This, this was a part-time role for some guy to play. This is just some guy dressed up like Martha Washington once in a while
You know, it was not a full-time job, especially back then. They didn't even live in the White House
Anyway, so it's just a like a fictional character kind of like they all are do a certain degree. I mean, I'm a conspiracy
There is to a degree
Like when I connect dots that maybe shouldn't be connected
I don't know but certain dots like when I see that they put every black man and the movies in the dress at some point
In Korea, I'll be connecting them down like why all these brothers don't wear a dress. That's happening to me
Dave Chappelle another great comedian said that you know in the industry they tried to make him wear a dress
Have you ever ran into that with with scripts and and if there's something that you know, you wouldn't do you know for
I definitely haven't ran enough to put on the dress.
I mean, you know, you have to have,
you have to have boundaries.
You have to have limits that you refuse to cross.
You know, for me, I know what they are.
They've yet to been challenged.
So, you know, I don't have to speak on them.
I was asked to dribble a basketball.
on the talk show this morning, like you said earlier.
That's not that I was addressed, but I was like,
no, I'm gonna look stupid the other day.
You gotta know that you're a brand.
I'm a brand.
You need to protect your brand at all times.
When things happen that can possibly affect your brand,
your brand can be diminished
and you don't want that to happen.
So protecting my brand is definitely a priority.
And here come the Cardinals, and from the looks of it, the New Pope is not Turks since.
The New Pope is nine-year-old Oscar nominee,
Covenciane Wallace.
I don't think anyone saw this one coming.
It wasn't a full-time job to do this back then.
These days it kind of is.
But they've gotten better at the technology and the technique here.
Put on this this clothes and in posed for a painting. That's all it is
That's all that's like a part-time job. Maybe once or twice a year somebody plays the part of Martha, Washington
And now I'm gonna venture off into speculation. This is scientifically
Make sure she's in the back for the group photo Viola was facing a fate worse than death
Sorry mom, I have a strict no ruffles policy.
Until her twin brother Sebastian.
Where are you going?
London, for a couple of weeks.
What are you gonna do about school?
I was kinda hoping you could help me with that.
Showed her a way out.
Could you just like, pretend to be me?
Why, turn you into your brother?
Nobody in L.A.R.E. has even met Sebastian.
They wouldn't know the difference.
Now, she's headed to L.A.R.E. Academy.
Let's go, kick.
Where the men have gained, and the women have attitude.
They're pretty ladies.
Ew, girls with butts like mine do not talk to boys with faces like yours.
We're gonna be tight, bro!
Seriously, how old are you?
I skipped a couple grades.
There's something on about that new boy.
You are so busted!
But at this school, everyone's got a secret.
Duke wants Olivia.
What do you like?
She is who wants a bastion.
Isn't he cute?
How you doin', babe?
Woo!
Who is really Viola, whose brother is dating Monique.
So she hates Olivia, who's dating Duke, to make Sebastian jealous.
What did your heart tell you?
I mean, which one would you rather see naked?
He is really Viola getting jealous, because she wants Duke, who thinks she's a guy.
Okay, okay.
And this is where it gets really complicated.
Oh boy.
Sexual tension.
Male-female dynamics.
The high school experience.
The pain.
I hate high school.
Is it just me or does this soccer game have more nudity than most?
This free.
They're not really good at talking girls.
Wow, you're hot.
What?
You know, you're a human guy.
Man, gunman.
The secret is out.
Amanda Bynes, Alex Brackenrich, Channing Tatum,
Robert Hoffman, Vinnie Jones, Laura Ramsey,
and David Cross.
I got lady troubles.
I got a left time of knowledge.
She's the man.
Oh, oh, oh, right.
All right, now I'll check out the symbolism
of Freemasonry, written by...
Albert Mackey, 1882. All the deities of pagan antiquity, however numerous they may be, can always be reduced to the two different forms of the generative principle, the active or male and the passive or female.
Hence, the gods were always arranged in pairs as Jupiter and Juno, Bacchus and Venus, Osiris and Isis, etc.
But the ancients went further, believing that the procreative and productive powers of nature might be conceived to exist in the same individual.
Who was first lady George Washington? I just wonder why they put these aprons on there with the square in compass
That looks like a blade. I do suspect if these people are male that they are castrated
All right, there's Gaia. That's G for Gaia and the other that's the point within the circle
This is the radiant circle of the light the androgynous atom
this message. What is the See Her Award? It's an award designed to recognize the
importance of accurately portraying women across the entertainment landscape.
It's extremely challenging to strive for fairness and parody across all
genders and to face and expose their greatest fears and push through them.
You don't need more or better leaders. We need someone willing to fight.
but in the form of a real woman in every way
and inspiring the heroes who are going to save this world.
As part of this movement, we created the hashtag SeeHerAward
to honor women who embody the values of empathy, resilience, and courage.
I truly believe that the privilege of a lifetime is being who you are.
And it was clear to me that I wanted to portray a strong and independent woman, a real one.
The irony in this...
CL is pretty simple, so that's why I designed it completely.
For the male specifically, but their time is up. We don't need them anymore
We can do better
We wanted her to be universal to be an inspiration to all people all around the world
And our plan was to make sure we didn't give too much attention to the fact that she's a woman
So I want all the girls watching here and now to know that a new day
His three-year-old saw the movie and when the movie ended the boy said